我发送了一封带有很长附件的电子邮件，你们很吵
I sent an email with a very long attachments and the noise you guys
attachments and the noise you guys receiveth it were true
接受，这是最好的阅读，这是真的
receiveth it were true okay that is the the best reading
okay that is the the best reading basically improbably free graphical
基本上不可能的免费图形模型，在某些情况下我知道它是基本的
basically improbably free graphical models that I know Elementary in some
models that I know Elementary in some sense but standard if you see pixels
感觉正常但是如果看到像素缺失
sense but standard if you see pixels missing
missing don't start sending me all you know that
不要开始向我发送所有您知道该页面丢失的信息，以及该页面丢失的信息
don't start sending me all you know that page is missing well that page missing
page is missing well that page missing because it's missing right that's what
因为它缺少权利，这就是您下载收入中国时发生的情况
because it's missing right that's what happens when you download income China
happens when you download income China okay some pages are missing
好吧，有些页面丢失了，我只是在开玩笑，但是你知道一些页面
okay some pages are missing I'm just kidding but you know some pages
I'm just kidding but you know some pages don't exist actually
根本不存在好吧，报价还没有完成
don't exist actually okay the offer has not completed them
okay the offer has not completed them yet especially energy to things like
尤其是像那样的事情
yet especially energy to things like that
that alright so what I think I realize we're
好吧，所以我想我意识到我们的发展非常缓慢，也许
alright so what I think I realize we're going extremely slowly and maybe is
going extremely slowly and maybe is because I don't want the class to drop
因为我不希望班上课之前就放弃
because I don't want the class to drop it before even the first homework is due
it before even the first homework is due or something like that okay but for sure
或类似的东西，但可以肯定的是，我们需要加快作业速度
or something like that okay but for sure we need to accelerate the homeworks
we need to accelerate the homeworks otherwise advanced years doing six for
不然的话，高年级就可以为多服务年做6年了，所以下一个工作
otherwise advanced years doing six for multiservice year okay so next one work
multiservice year okay so next one work is view made basically you know
是基本上使视图变得像星期五的一些物流一样您知道吗
is view made basically you know okay like some logistics here on Friday
okay like some logistics here on Friday we're not gonna have recitation but
我们不会朗诵，但苏比克（Subic）将会在这间办公室里
we're not gonna have recitation but Subic is going to be in this office in
Subic is going to be in this office in 311 Cushing 3 Devon I think it says
311 Cushing 3 Devon我认为是乙醇盐311 M ok在选举期间
311 Cushing 3 Devon I think it says ethoxide 311 M ok during the election
ethoxide 311 M ok during the election time and the purpose of the homework is
时间和功课的目的是每个人都要做，即使我们有
time and the purpose of the homework is for everybody to do it even if we have
for everybody to do it even if we have to give you the solution ok so you
给你好的解决方案，所以你基本上不能离开房间
to give you the solution ok so you cannot leave basically the room on
cannot leave basically the room on Friday without having a solution down
星期五，如果没有解决的办法，那是没有任何事情的。
Friday without having a solution down there is no sort of thing all it's a
there is no sort of thing all it's a difficult problem I will leave it for
困难的问题，我将其留待以后我们希望您这样做，即使那样
difficult problem I will leave it for later we want you to do it even if that
later we want you to do it even if that means you asked him for the solution ok
表示您要求他提供解决方案，好吧，我们要在星期一完成，我不在了，
means you asked him for the solution ok we want it done on Monday I'm away and
we want it done on Monday I'm away and Subic is going to give the recitation
苏比克（Subic）将会把功课的叙述给我们，希望我们
Subic is going to give the recitation for homework to that we hope it would be
for homework to that we hope it would be posted this weekend okay so the very
可以在这个周末发布，所以周一和周五是作业2的专用站
posted this weekend okay so the very station for homework 2 on Monday and
station for homework 2 on Monday and then I will take the lecture on Friday
然后我偶尔会在星期五上课，而我的意思是星期四，
then I will take the lecture on Friday occasionally when I mean Thursday and
occasionally when I mean Thursday and Friday will give the lecture next week
星期五将在下周好的授课中，所以我们今天要做的是
Friday will give the lecture next week ok so what we do today is we need to
ok so what we do today is we need to discuss we need to go back to the
讨论我们需要回到消除算法开始
discuss we need to go back to the elimination algorithm poaches start off
elimination algorithm poaches start off very trivial but where we stopped was
非常琐碎，但我们停下来的地方是提供图理论的
very trivial but where we stopped was sort of to provide the graph theoretic
sort of to provide the graph theoretic approach to elimination I mean we said
消除方法我的意思是我们说我们消除了，现在您知道我们看到了移动设备
approach to elimination I mean we said we eliminate now you know we saw mobile
we eliminate now you know we saw mobile the potential to depend on the variables
取决于我们消除的变量的潜力，但正确的是
the potential to depend on the variables we eliminate but what is the right
we eliminate but what is the right ordering how we control the complexity
排序我们如何控制算法的复杂性以及如何执行此操作
ordering how we control the complexity of the algorithm and how we do this
of the algorithm and how we do this purely using graph theoretic approaches
纯粹使用尚未讨论的图论方法，因此我们和
purely using graph theoretic approaches that has not been discussed so we me and
that has not been discussed so we me and we have summarized very briefly the
我们已经简要总结了算法，所以我们记得我们是什么
we have summarized very briefly the algorithms so we remember what we are
algorithms so we remember what we are talking okay so the elimination
说话还可以，因此消除算法基本上具有以下特征
talking okay so the elimination algorithm basically has the following
algorithm basically has the following steps the first step is realized
步骤第一步实现
您必须选择一些排序，以便在查询中注明我们想要的
algorithm basically has the following steps the first step is realized
you have to choose some ordering where the query notes we want that you want
您必须选择一些排序，以便在查询中注明我们想要的
the query notes we want that you want basically to compute let's say the
基本上是为了计算，假设最后一次还可以，因此
basically to compute let's say the marginal of the last okay so the
marginal of the last okay so the ordering it starts out except F is the
排序开始，除了F是查询注释出现在最后，然后是
ordering it starts out except F is the query notes appears the last and then
query notes appears the last and then you have to create a list of acting
您必须创建一个表演列表
潜力，如果您喜欢，因为这是直接图表，因此您需要仔细检查每一个
query notes appears the last and then you have to create a list of acting
potentials if you like and because this is a direct graph you go through each
潜力，如果您喜欢，因为这是直接图表，因此您需要仔细检查每一个
is a direct graph you go through each node in the graph and you place all of
图中的节点，然后放置所有的条件概率
node in the graph and you place all of the conditional probabilities that
the conditional probabilities that define basically altogether the
基本上完全定义联合分配的大小写
define basically altogether the capitalization of the Joint Distribution
capitalization of the Joint Distribution you put them on what's called the
您将它们放到了现在称为“主动”的位置上
you put them on what's called the actively now in addition to those in the
actively now in addition to those in the second step when you call evidence you
第二步，当您召集证据时，您也将其放在活动列表中
second step when you call evidence you also put in the active list this
also put in the active list this evidence functions which were nothing
别无其他的证据功能代表了当然的功能
evidence functions which were nothing else present the functions of course
else present the functions of course this variable to take value five let's
这个变量取值为5，我们说对了，所以您实际上并不需要
this variable to take value five let's say right so so you don't really need to
say right so so you don't really need to have it explicitly but conceptualize
有明确的说明，但将其概念化，这需要放在某个地方，因此，如果
have it explicitly but conceptualize this this needs to come somewhere so if
this this needs to come somewhere so if you want it just a formal presentation
您只需要一个正式的演示文稿，基本上就需要提供此证据
you want it just a formal presentation basically you need to put this evidence
basically you need to put this evidence function right in the active list in
在此潜在条件版本中的活动列表中具有正确的功能
function right in the active list in editions of this condition of potential
editions of this condition of potential okay and then following your elimination
好，然后按照您的消除方法或您需要做的是
okay and then following your elimination or the what you need to do is you have
or the what you need to do is you have to go to every node X I following hot or
转到热或干之后的每个节点XI，您必须找到所有
to go to every node X I following hot or dry and you have to find all the
dry and you have to find all the potentials the depend on X high alright
电位取决于X高，所以基本上这将是证据
potentials the depend on X high alright so basically this will be the evidence
so basically this will be the evidence functions would be X I depending on
函数将是XI取决于孩子的指数
functions would be X I depending on exponent the children depending on
exponent the children depending on excise the excise the parent etc okay
父母，等等，好好下雪，将所有这些相乘
excise the excise the parent etc okay snow multiply all those together some
snow multiply all those together some elect I and then form a new potential
选出我，然后形成一个新的潜力，我们称其为XI，然后放置
elect I and then form a new potential which we call it the X I and then place
which we call it the X I and then place this potential in the activity and all
活动中的这种潜力以及所有其他潜在的潜力
this potential in the activity and all the other potentials basically that you
the other potentials basically that you introduced
介绍涉及它我将被删除
introduced that involve its I will be removed from
that involve its I will be removed from the after this okay so you'll be sucked
好的之后，您将被效果I和最后的效果所吸引
the after this okay so you'll be sucked into this with the effect I and the last
into this with the effect I and the last step is basically if you want to
步骤基本上是，如果您想标准化，您知道可以通过以下方法来执行此操作
step is basically if you want to normalize you know you can do this by
normalize you know you can do this by summing over all possible values of the
现在求和所有查询变量的可能值
summing over all possible values of the query variables now to be able to
query variables now to be able to introduce sort of a graph theoretic
不幸的是，介绍了该算法的某种图形理论版本
introduce sort of a graph theoretic version of this algorithm unfortunately
version of this algorithm unfortunately we have to discuss a little bit on how
我们必须讨论一下如何在无向中进行因式分解
we have to discuss a little bit on how we do factorization in in undirected
we do factorization in in undirected graphs which is actually my next lecture
图实际上是我的下一次演讲，所以我有点像
graphs which is actually my next lecture so I'm gonna be sort of the little
so I'm gonna be sort of the little header and go backwards right so you may
标头并向后退，所以您可能认为教育是正确的事情
header and go backwards right so you may think education is a right thing to do
think education is a right thing to do but in life not everything is the right
但是生活中并不是每件事都是正确的事，所以做一些事
but in life not everything is the right thing to do alright so doing some things
thing to do alright so doing some things how to fold the hem sometimes we need to
如何折叠下摆有时我们需要听一些东西以不同的顺序飞翔
how to fold the hem sometimes we need to hear something flies in different order
hear something flies in different order that can be helpful as well okay so
这也可能会有所帮助，所以让我们看看情况如何
that can be helpful as well okay so let's see where the situations so we're
let's see where the situations so we're going to discuss this elimination
将讨论这种消除算法的有向图和唯一
going to discuss this elimination algorithm directed graphs and the only
algorithm directed graphs and the only thing that I want you to know which will
我想让你知道的事情实际上将在下一堂课上讲
thing that I want you to know which will be actually on next lecture there is no
be actually on next lecture there is no conditional probabilities general
条件概率一般有向图
conditional probabilities general directed graphs the way we have them in
directed graphs the way we have them in directed graphs what you have is you
有向图您现在所拥有的就是您的潜力
directed graphs what you have is you have potential over the status now you
have potential over the status now you have product of potentials over the sets
在互连节点集上具有势积，我们称之为
have product of potentials over the sets of interconnected nodes which we call
of interconnected nodes which we call them clicks okay and those potentials
他们点击就可以了，那些潜力并不是真正的概率分布
them clicks okay and those potentials are not really probability distributions
are not really probability distributions all right which means they're not they
好吧，这意味着他们不是他们没有规范化或他们没有
all right which means they're not they don't normalize or they don't have the
don't normalize or they don't have the physical meaning that the conditional
条件分布在有向图中的物理含义
physical meaning that the conditional distributions have in in directed graphs
distributions have in in directed graphs so in this undirected graph here if you
因此，在此无向图中，如果您要寻找集团
so in this undirected graph here if you look for the number of cliques the
look for the number of cliques the maximal cliques that somebody can have
某人可以拥有的最大集团是X 1 X 2是集团
maximal cliques that somebody can have is you can see X 1 X 2 is a clique
is you can see X 1 X 2 is a clique they're connected X 1 X 3 is a clique X
它们是相连的X 1 X 3是集团X 3 X 5是特征X 2 X 5和X 6是
they're connected X 1 X 3 is a clique X 3 X 5 is a trait X 2 X 5 and X 6 is a
3 X 5 is a trait X 2 X 5 and X 6 is a clique
派系和x2 x4实际上还可以X 1 X 2 X 5
clique and x2 x4 is actually okay X 1 X 2 X 5
and x2 x4 is actually okay X 1 X 2 X 5 it is not a clique because the X 1 and X
这不是集团，因为X 1和X 5没有连接好，所以最大
it is not a clique because the X 1 and X 5 are not connected okay so the maximal
5 are not connected okay so the maximal cliques are basically the ones that are
派系基本上是这里列出的派系，我想让你做的唯一一件事
cliques are basically the ones that are listed here the only thing I want you to
listed here the only thing I want you to know in the context of undirected graphs
知道在无向图的上下文中，基本上
know in the context of undirected graphs basically the Joint Distribution for the
basically the Joint Distribution for the variables will be written as the product
变量将被写为已定义的某些电位的乘积
variables will be written as the product of some potentials that are defined
of some potentials that are defined using the variables over its clique and
在其派系中使用变量，我们不会为您提供任何具体信息
using the variables over its clique and we will not give you any specific
we will not give you any specific details but they are can be anything the
细节，但是它们可以是任何东西，实际上唯一的限制是它们
details but they are can be anything the only constraint actually is that they
only constraint actually is that they are positive so effectively when you
是积极的，那么当你乘以它们时，你就有机会
are positive so effectively when you multiply them you get a probability
multiply them you get a probability distribution which will not be
分布将不会被规范化，但这是我唯一的事情
distribution which will not be normalized but that's the only thing I
normalized but that's the only thing I want you to understand so for example if
希望您理解，例如，如果这与之前的示例相同
want you to understand so for example if this is the same example with it earlier
this is the same example with it earlier but I am showing this form directly
但是如果您想找到
but I am showing this form directly graphs if you want to find the joint of
graphs if you want to find the joint of X 1 and X 6 4 X 6 is given so that's an
给出了X 1和X 6 4 X 6，这是一个证据节点，您需要做的是
X 1 and X 6 4 X 6 is given so that's an evidence node what you need to do is you
evidence node what you need to do is you have to write the you know you have to
必须写你知道你必须普及所有的联合概率
have to write the you know you have to popularize the joint probability of all
popularize the joint probability of all the variables and integrate everything
变量，然后将除X 1和X 6之外的所有内容整合到一起
the variables and integrate everything out except X 1 and X 6 you have to
out except X 1 and X 6 you have to integrate X 2 X 3 X 4 X 5 6 X 6 to the
将X 2 X 3 X 4 X 5 6 X 6集成到具有此证据功能的X
integrate X 2 X 3 X 4 X 5 6 X 6 to the with this evidence function to these X
with this evidence function to these X bar sticks and you notice we instead of
棒棒，您会注意到我们而不是这里的概率我具有这种潜力
bar sticks and you notice we instead of probabilities here I have this potential
probabilities here I have this potential function this is the way we define
函数，这就是我们一次又一次定义无向图的方式
function this is the way we define undirected graphs ok and again as I said
undirected graphs ok and again as I said we will see this slowly in the following
我们将在今天开始的下一次演讲中慢慢看到这一点，但我希望您能
we will see this slowly in the following lecture we start today but I want you to
lecture we start today but I want you to sleep now because I'm going to use some
现在睡吧，因为我将使用无向图的一些想法，并且已经
sleep now because I'm going to use some ideas from undirected graphs and already
ideas from undirected graphs and already following the elimination algorithm so
遵循消除算法，所以有条件的概率
following the elimination algorithm so the probability of conditional
the probability of conditional probabilities but the rest the
概率，但其余的操作则将一些
probabilities but the rest the operations of putting some of the
operations of putting some of the summations in words and in order of
单词的总和和节点的消除顺序对于
summations in words and in order of elimination of the nodes is the same for
elimination of the nodes is the same for both sets of graphs so for example here
两组图形，例如，在这里您知道让X 6固定于此
both sets of graphs so for example here you know let's see X 6 is fixed to this
you know let's see X 6 is fixed to this value
值还可以，但我相信您会在我注意到时
value okay but I believe you notice when I
okay but I believe you notice when I guess this Lent the function the idea is
猜猜这借了功能的想法将要使用您的渲染功能
guess this Lent the function the idea is going to use the render function you
going to use the render function you will have to sound 1x6 right so when you
将必须正确听起来1x6，所以当您为X的所有可能值发出声音时，
will have to sound 1x6 right so when you sound for all possible values of X takes
sound for all possible values of X takes only when you hit this X bar six this
仅当您击中该X竖线6时，该值将为非零，因此其余值为非零
only when you hit this X bar six this would be nonzero so the rest is non zero
would be nonzero so the rest is non zero so this summation sort of gets you only
因此，这种求和方式只能使您获得与此条形对应的一个值
so this summation sort of gets you only one value corresponding to this bar
one value corresponding to this bar value there okay so so the summation X 6
值在那里好，所以总和X 6不是我已经在第二行中输入的值
value there okay so so the summation X 6 is not some of the second line I already
is not some of the second line I already put the evidence here and then I have to
将证据放到这里，然后我必须召唤X 5我们的Explorer X 3和X
put the evidence here and then I have to summon X 5 that our Explorer X 3 and X
summon X 5 that our Explorer X 3 and X few and you notice here I have
很少，您会注意到这里我具有涉及节点3 5的潜力
few and you notice here I have potentials that involve the nodes 3 5
potentials that involve the nodes 3 5 all right and two five and six two five
好吧，两个五个和六个两个五个和六个好吧，我将总结一下
all right and two five and six two five and six okay and I'm going to sum in
and six okay and I'm going to sum in five and I call this exactly as we did
五，我称呼它就像我们对有向图所做的那样真正的快速五
five and I call this exactly as we did with directed graphs real quick five
with directed graphs real quick five subscript and whatever notes are left
下标和任何剩余的音符，让我们听听剩下的X 5是
subscript and whatever notes are left let's hear what is left there are X 5 is
let's hear what is left there are X 5 is Delta X 6 X has some specific body
Delta X 6 X有一些特定的身体选择，没有兴趣的是X 2 X 3全部
Delta X 6 X has some specific body choice of no interest is X 2 X 3 all
choice of no interest is X 2 X 3 all right so this doesn't involve any
对，所以当我进行求和时，这不涉及任何表达式
right so this doesn't involve any expression when I do the summation and
expression when I do the summation and export is exactly this before I get
出口正是这种情况，之后我又有另一种潜在的恐惧去探索
export is exactly this before I get another potential fear of explore the
another potential fear of explore the defense on your legs to then I have to
防守，然后我必须在X 3中解决该产品，然后我
defense on your legs to then I have to solve this product in X 3 and then I
solve this product in X 3 and then I have to sum everything in X 2 this is
必须将X 2中的所有内容相加，这是归一化因子，所以当
have to sum everything in X 2 this is the normalization factor right so when
the normalization factor right so when we write it like that the distribution
我们这样写，即分布被归一化，所以我们必须放一些
we write it like that the distribution is normalized so we have to put some
is normalized so we have to put some normalization factor and effectively if
归一化因子，如果要查找条件写则有效
normalization factor and effectively if you want to find the conditional write
you want to find the conditional write once you compute this in the condition
一旦您在条件中计算出此值，它就会与之成比例，因此您可以
once you compute this in the condition will be proportional to that so you can
will be proportional to that so you can normalize by summing this potential
通过将所有潜在值的潜在期间视图相加来归一化
normalize by summing this potential period view over all possible values of
period view over all possible values of x1 okay so the rest even under extra
x1好的，所以即使是额外的课，其余的也没有任何区别
x1 okay so the rest even under extra class don't really have any difference
class don't really have any difference when it comes to the implementation of
关于我们的标准消除算法的实现，但是
when it comes to the implementation of our standard elimination algorithm but
our standard elimination algorithm but they will help us to do this sort of
他们将帮助我们以图形方式完成这种工作，
they will help us to do this sort of graphically okay and and it would be
graphically okay and and it would be easier way not only to conserve to get
更简便的方法，不仅可以保存正确的概念，还可以
easier way not only to conserve to get the concept here right but also to
the concept here right but also to Graham this and implemented let me see
格雷厄姆（Graham）这样执行，让我看看我在这里还有话要说吗
Graham this and implemented let me see if I have anything else to say here okay
if I have anything else to say here okay so again the only difference is not
因此，唯一的区别不是条件概率，而是潜力
so again the only difference is not conditional probabilities but potentials
conditional probabilities but potentials defined over maximal cliques and I told
定义了最大的集团，我告诉您您在这里获得了多少点击
defined over maximal cliques and I told you how many clicks you have here one
you how many clicks you have here one two three four and five clicks okay this
两三四和五次点击好，这是无向图，所以好
two three four and five clicks okay this is what undirected graphs it's okay so
is what undirected graphs it's okay so we need a graphical way that somehow
我们需要一种图形化的方式来以某种方式帮助我们控制复杂性
we need a graphical way that somehow helps us to control the complexity of
helps us to control the complexity of the eliminate algorithm so we need to
消除算法，所以我们需要看看我们如何做到这一点，我
the eliminate algorithm so we need to see how we're gonna do this and I'm
see how we're gonna do this and I'm going to start with this I deal with a
从这个开始，我将讨论一个不属于控球后卫的问题
going to start with this I deal with a point guard elimination which is not of
point guard elimination which is not of the graph analog of the elimination
我们已经看到的消除算法的图形类似物，但我要
the graph analog of the elimination algorithm we have seen but I am gonna
algorithm we have seen but I am gonna post this for undirected graphs for a
将其发布给无向图是有原因的，然后我将概括一下
post this for undirected graphs for a reason and then I will generalize the
reason and then I will generalize the directed graphs
有向图好吧，让我们看看这是否是一部分
directed graphs okay so let's see if this is part
理论上的，所以我们有图G的消除或驱使
theoretical so we have an elimination or drive for graph G and the elimination
drive for graph G and the elimination the gutter elimination algorithm white
排水沟消除算法白色统治
the gutter elimination algorithm white domination does the trick
domination does the trick it says probably no reasoning
它说可能没有推理消除规则可以连接所有
it says probably no reasoning elimination rule is connect all if it's
elimination rule is connect all if it's very boots and then let me move excite
非常长的靴子，然后让我从图中移开兴奋点，然后将它放成蓝色
very boots and then let me move excite from the graph and I put this in blue
from the graph and I put this in blue for the purpose connect all the
为此，将XI的所有邻居和XI的邻居
for the purpose connect all the neighbors of X I and the neighbors of
neighbors of X I and the neighbors of the graph is the DEF neighbors so that's
该图是DEF邻居，所以这是一个赠款概念，与您拥有的不一样
the graph is the DEF neighbors so that's a grant concept it's not like you have
a grant concept it's not like you have ever seen you say the patterns from the
没看过你说过孩子们的模式，你只知道图形损坏
ever seen you say the patterns from the kids and you know just the graph damage
kids and you know just the graph damage okay
好吧，所以您连接了所有邻居，
okay so you connect all the neighbors and
so you connect all the neighbors and then we move excite from the graph so
然后我们从图表中移动兴奋，让我们来看看这件事是如何工作的
then we move excite from the graph so let's take how this thing works
let's take how this thing works graphically so let's say we want this is
以图形方式表示，假设我们希望这是我们想要的消除顺序
graphically so let's say we want this is the elimination order we want to
the elimination order we want to eliminate first let's fix then X 5 X 4 X
首先消除，让我们修复，然后再消除X 5 X 4 X 3 X 2 X 1，以便消除X 6
eliminate first let's fix then X 5 X 4 X 3 X 2 X 1 so to eliminate X 6
3 X 2 X 1 so to eliminate X 6 what do we need to do
我们需要做些什么消除算法，看一下
what do we need to do elimination algorithm look at the
elimination algorithm look at the neighbors the neighbors have two and
邻居邻居的水里有两个和五个
neighbors the neighbors have two and five in the water the neighborhood's
five in the water the neighborhood's collective then we eliminated six we get
然后我们消除了六个，我们在下一个节点的地球中得到了这个
collective then we eliminated six we get this then in our earth of the next node
this then in our earth of the next node is expired before we eliminate expired
在我们消除过期之前已过期，请查看名称与X 2和X的关系
is expired before we eliminate expired would look at the name versus X 2 and X
would look at the name versus X 2 and X 3 we connect them and then with what we
3我们将它们连接起来，然后对X 5进行操作，然后消除下一个节点
3 we connect them and then with what we do to X 5 eliminate then our next node
do to X 5 eliminate then our next node is explore the neighbor is X 2 there is
正在探索的邻居是X 2，没有必要建立链接，所以我们
is explore the neighbor is X 2 there is nothing no need to put a link so we
nothing no need to put a link so we eliminate X 4 which is list then the
消除列表中的X 4，然后像这样下一个固定的X 3，然后消除X 1
eliminate X 4 which is list then the next fixed X 3 like this and then X 1
next fixed X 3 like this and then X 1 the key thing here is the following step
关键是接下来的步骤，我们以某种方式与
the key thing here is the following step that somehow we connect with the
that somehow we connect with the neighbors all right and who else did we
邻居很好，我们还和谁联系了，所以这是
neighbors all right and who else did we connect the neighbors so this was
connect the neighbors so this was eliminated and then this thing here but
消除，然后在这里将其连接但将节点2和3连接起来
eliminated and then this thing here but connected nodes 2 &amp; 3
connected nodes 2 &amp; 3 okay and again the concept of the
好吧，邻国权利的概念是一个很好的政治
okay and again the concept of the neighbors right is is a good political
neighbors right is is a good political concept in the context of undirected
在无向图的上下文中的概念现在您会注意到，每次
concept in the context of undirected graphs now you notice that each time a
graphs now you notice that each time a node is eliminated all of its neighbors
节点被消除，其所有邻居均正确连接，形成一个
node is eliminated all of its neighbors are correct are connected forming a
are correct are connected forming a clique that's what we call the
派系，这就是我们所说的消除小河，例如这里
clique that's what we call the elimination Creek so for example here
elimination Creek so for example here when I connect now student 5 2 5 &amp; 6 is
当我现在连接时，学生5 2 5＆6是一个集团完全连接的节点集
when I connect now student 5 2 5 &amp; 6 is a clique fully connected set of nodes
a clique fully connected set of nodes ok when I go in and connect to a 3 2 or
确定，当我进入并连接到3 2或3＆5时，单击确定，这就是
ok when I go in and connect to a 3 2 or 3 &amp; 5 is the click ok so that is the
3 &amp; 5 is the click ok so that is the elimination click and it is very
消除点击，这很重要，您可以将其与
elimination click and it is very important you can connect this back with
important you can connect this back with the elimination algorithm we discussed
我们之前讨论过的消除算法，但是现在我们将在
the elimination algorithm we discussed before but we will see this now in a in
before but we will see this now in a in a graphical reading fashion so for
图形化的阅读方式，例如
a graphical reading fashion so for example in in
example in in you know there clicks but we generated
您知道有点击，但我们在上一个示例中生成的是此点击
you know there clicks but we generated in the previous example is this click
in the previous example is this click two five and six and I could exist six
两个五个和六个，我可能存在六个，因为它对应于第六个节点
two five and six and I could exist six because it corresponds to node six right
because it corresponds to node six right this is the note that I'm going to
这是我要从此点击中消除的音符，但这是
this is the note that I'm going to eliminate from this click but this is
eliminate from this click but this is the click two five and six right and
点击右二五和六，然后又产生了一次点击
the click two five and six right and there is another click that I generated
there is another click that I generated which is two three and five and I call
这是两个三和五个，我称其为5c五个，因为我要
which is two three and five and I call it 5c five because I'm going to
it 5c five because I'm going to eliminate no time okay so three powerful
消除时间没问题，所以这三种强大的访问程序消除算法
eliminate no time okay so three powerful visiting program elimination algorithm
visiting program elimination algorithm is that it's time to remove a node if
如果您记录了以下节点的集合，那么该是删除节点的时候了
is that it's time to remove a node if you record the collection of nodes that
you record the collection of nodes that are the neighbors of X I at that moment
是那个时候XI的邻居，包括兴奋的自我，这是
are the neighbors of X I at that moment including excite self which are this
including excite self which are this maximal leaks that are formed during the
消除算法期间形成的最大泄漏
maximal leaks that are formed during the elimination algorithm okay
没什么，因为您打算在要做的时候正确地进行操作
nothing because the operations you're going to do right when you are going to
going to do right when you are going to eliminate the note you are going to
消除基本上要与之相乘的音符，我将使用
eliminate the note you are going to multiply basically I'm gonna work with
multiply basically I'm gonna work with the potentials from districts so the
来自各地区的潜力，因此点击的规模越大，越多
the potentials from districts so the biggest the size of the click the more
biggest the size of the click the more complex the algorithm will be and that's
算法将会很复杂，这就是为什么最大的集团，但是您
complex the algorithm will be and that's why the largest clique but that you
why the largest clique but that you can't with defines the order of complex
无法定义算法的复杂字段的顺序
can't with defines the order of complex fields the of the algorithm
fields the of the algorithm okay so nowadays basically the maximum
好吧，所以现在基本上希腊人的最大人数是3，所以
okay so nowadays basically the maximum size of the Greeks is 3 so that will
size of the Greeks is 3 so that will define the complexity of the output so
定义输出的复杂度，所以让我们说它是否不包含K值
define the complexity of the output so let's say if it's not takes K values
let's say if it's not takes K values this could be gave the power 3 so case
这可以赋予3的幂，所以在前面的讲座中我们看到的是
this could be gave the power 3 so case what we saw in the earlier lecture is
what we saw in the earlier lecture is defined as the 3 width of the graph okay
定义为图的3个宽度
defined as the 3 width of the graph okay okay so this is dependence masking even
okay so this is dependence masking even a maximum size the size of the maximum
最大大小实现时获得的最大派系的大小
a maximum size the size of the maximum clique that you get when you implement
clique that you get when you implement this graph lumination output okay
这个图的发光输出还可以
好的，所以我在前面的子弹上看这里，它说
clique that you get when you implement this graph lumination output okay
all right so so the I'm looking here on the front bullet right so it says the
好的，所以我在前面的子弹上看这里，它说
the front bullet right so it says the elimination of the node has the effect
消除节点的作用是在所有节点之间创建新的依赖关系
elimination of the node has the effect of creating new dependencies between all
of creating new dependencies between all pairs of neighbors thus introducing a
对邻居，从而在图中引入了一个新的集团，所以这里的想法
pairs of neighbors thus introducing a new clique in the graph so the idea here
new clique in the graph so the idea here is by saying connect the neighbors of X
通过说连接X 6的邻居以某种方式使节点2和5变成现在
is by saying connect the neighbors of X 6 somehow nodes 2 &amp; 5 become now
6 somehow nodes 2 &amp; 5 become now dependent and in some circumstances you
依赖，在某些情况下，您将看不到它，说哈哈
dependent and in some circumstances you won't be able to see it say ha there is
won't be able to see it say ha there is a relation of nodes 2 &amp; 5 right I'm
对不起，节点2和节点5的关系很抱歉，是的
a relation of nodes 2 &amp; 5 right I'm sorry yeah
sorry yeah no it's two in five I mean they're on
不，五分之二是我的意思是它们位于图形系统的另一端，但是
no it's two in five I mean they're on the other side of this graph system but
the other side of this graph system but somehow if you're going to eliminate X
以某种方式，如果您打算在消除X的过程中消除X X
somehow if you're going to eliminate X this X 6 during to reduce these
this X 6 during to reduce these dependencies between nodes 5 and we will
节点5之间的依赖关系，我们会说，如果我们不执行此步骤，
dependencies between nodes 5 and we will say if you don't do this step when we
say if you don't do this step when we work with with directed graphs basically
使用有向图基本上，您将无法对此建模
work with with directed graphs basically you will not be able to model this
you will not be able to model this correctly ok
没关系，所以在这种情况下，您会注意到
correctly ok so in this particular case you notice
so in this particular case you notice you for voluntary angular's right and
您出于自愿角的权利，这就是为什么这个过程正在酝酿中
you for voluntary angular's right and that's why this process is contouring
that's why this process is contouring relation of the graph for an undirected
对于我们连接的无向图，该图的关系您知道
relation of the graph for an undirected graph where we connect you know the
graph where we connect you know the inventor of elimination we connect the
消除的发明者，我们连接了要消除的节点的邻居
inventor of elimination we connect the neighbors of the node to be eliminated
neighbors of the node to be eliminated forming these cliques lexical list can
形成这些集团词法列表的方式可以扩展到，但请在此之前注意
forming these cliques lexical list can be extended to but notice here before
be extended to but notice here before you say okay transformation of directed
您说可以对有向图进行转换，然后应用无向图
you say okay transformation of directed graph and then apply the undirected
graph and then apply the undirected graph elimination algorithm there is an
图消除算法有一个中间步骤，在上一步中
graph elimination algorithm there is an intermediate step and in previous step
intermediate step and in previous step that's extremely important it says where
这是非常重要的，它说医生在哪里，然后将其转化为
that's extremely important it says where is the doctor and then transform it to
is the doctor and then transform it to an undirected graph about sort of a very
如果您错过了该步骤，则这将是一个关于非常棘手的概念的无向图
an undirected graph about sort of a very tricky concept if you miss the step
tricky concept if you miss the step basically this Albert do not work so the
基本上这个阿尔伯特不起作用，所以这里的想法不是简单地改变它
basically this Albert do not work so the idea here is not simply to transform it
idea here is not simply to transform it an undirected graph but you have to
无向图，但您必须保湿并提醒我
an undirected graph but you have to moisturize it and remind me which
moisturize it and remind me which modernization here let's make the
在这里进行现代化改造，让父母基本可以，所以这里的想法
modernization here let's make the parents basically okay so the idea here
parents basically okay so the idea here is for example we need to connect the
例如，我们需要连接父母，比如说6和2＆5
is for example we need to connect the parents let's say of 6 which is 2 &amp; 5
parents let's say of 6 which is 2 &amp; 5 and then transform this to an undirected
然后将其转换为无向图，你知道下一个奎师那是
and then transform this to an undirected graph can you know the next krishna is
graph can you know the next krishna is basically the so pictorially why if you
基本上是这样，从图形上讲，如果不执行此步骤，为什么会一团糟
basically the so pictorially why if you don't do this step you would be messing
don't do this step you would be messing things up but can anybody basically just
问题，但是任何人基本上都可以停止思考为什么要注意这一点吗？
things up but can anybody basically just stop thinking why that step is attention
不，但是我们记得在无向图中的，我们还连接了
no but we remembered in the in the in the undirected graph we also connect the
the undirected graph we also connect the neighbors right so somebody will say
邻居说得对，所以有人会说我限制X 6 2和5为
neighbors right so somebody will say when let's say I limit X 6 2 &amp; 5 will be
when let's say I limit X 6 2 &amp; 5 will be neighbors I'm going to connect them so
邻居，我要联系他们，所以有了现代化，所以我采取了
neighbors I'm going to connect them so there is the modernization so I took
there is the modernization so I took care of it
关心它，为什么我需要道德化
care of it so why do I need to moralize
我们说的是好像在第一个循环中，但是因为在这里我们收集了
we're saying is it seems like in first loop but because here we collect the
loop but because here we collect the neighbors that maybe this does already
邻居，也许这确实已经妖魔化了
neighbors that maybe this does already demonisation does it
我的意思是让我们不要只是想像不到网络而已
I mean let's not go through that it to the net right that's not just imagining
the net right that's not just imagining things so then we can bypass many of
因此我们可以绕过以下幻灯片中的许多内容，所以让我们
things so then we can bypass many of them of the following slides so let's
them of the following slides so let's say we make this an undirected graph
说我们使它成为一个无向图好吧，所以我们连接了Rene，但我
say we make this an undirected graph alright okay so we connect Rene but I'm
alright okay so we connect Rene but I'm sorry this is okay so in this case this
抱歉，这还可以，所以在这种情况下，这是我的台词。
sorry this is okay so in this case this is this distant my lines okay I this
is this distant my lines okay I this will not work my god okay so let's see
我的天哪行不通，所以让我们看一下这个例子，如果有分钟x6
will not work my god okay so let's see here's the example if any minute x6
here's the example if any minute x6 the way we did it before there's not
在没有任何问题之前我们做的方式，所以让我去做
the way we did it before there's not gonna be any issue right so let me do
gonna be any issue right so let me do the following let me try one in
以下让我尝试终止x6，因为不会有
the following let me try one in terminating x6 because there will not be
terminating x6 because there will not be able to how we're different some
能够使我们与众不同一些组织确实说我们消除了
able to how we're different some organization does let's say we eliminate
organization does let's say we eliminate X Pfeiffer was it you go back to this
X Pfeiffer是您回到这张幻灯片并消除X 5并说我们
X Pfeiffer was it you go back to this slide and eliminate X 5 and let's say we
slide and eliminate X 5 and let's say we don't do any monetization so if you
不要做任何货币化，所以如果你不否认实现而转移
don't do any monetization so if you don't deny realization and you transfer
don't deny realization and you transfer this to you know to an undirected graph
据您所知，对于无向图，您要做的第一件事是什么
this to you know to an undirected graph what is the first thing you're going to
what is the first thing you're going to do on this guy so there's no
对这个人做，所以这里没有现代化，所以如果我
do on this guy so there's no modernization here right so if I
modernization here right so if I eliminate X 5 what needs to happen in
消除X 5无向图算法中需要发生的事情
eliminate X 5 what needs to happen in the undirected graph algorithm
邻居是否还活着
whether the neighbor survived
所以让我向您展示计算权，这是无向图，所以如果
so we let me show you the calculation right this is the undirected graph so if
right this is the undirected graph so if I'm going to eliminate X 5 what we need
我要消除X 5，我们需要做的是求和X 5
I'm going to eliminate X 5 what we need to do is we need to sum or X 5 the
to do is we need to sum or X 5 the following conditional distributions
给定X 3正确和X 6，以下条件分布已过期
following conditional distributions expired given X 3 all right and X 6
expired given X 3 all right and X 6 given X 2 X 5 we read this from the
给定X 2 X 5，我们从有向图上读取它，所以基本上是一种方法或
given X 2 X 5 we read this from the directed graph so basically one way or
directed graph so basically one way or another this is the calculation that we
另一个是我们需要做的计算，当您查看此内容时
another this is the calculation that we need to do and when you look at this
need to do and when you look at this calculation with X 5 integrated out who
使用X 5进行集成计算，现在谁获得了哪个节点之间的依赖关系
calculation with X 5 integrated out who now get dependencies between which node
now get dependencies between which node X 2 X 3 and X 6 so let me see this X 2 X
X 2 X 3和X 6，所以让我看看X 2 X 3和XX 6是依赖关系
X 2 X 3 and X 6 so let me see this X 2 X 3 and X X 6 is that dependency going to
3 and X X 6 is that dependency going to be there when we use just the undirected
当我们只使用无向图消除算法而没有
be there when we use just the undirected graph elimination algorithm without
graph elimination algorithm without realization so again we have a
再次意识到X 2 X 3和X 6 X 2 X之间存在依赖关系
realization so again we have a dependence between X 2 X 3 and X 6 X 2 X
dependence between X 2 X 3 and X 6 X 2 X 3 and X fixed
3和X固定
应用无向图消除时会丢失什么
dependence between X 2 X 3 and X 6 X 2 X 3 and X fixed
what is going to be missing when I apply they the undirected graph elimination
应用无向图消除时会丢失什么
they the undirected graph elimination algorithm so I need the dependency
算法，所以我需要x2 x3和x6之间的依赖关系，所以如果您这样做
algorithm so I need the dependency between x2 x3 and x6 so if you do this
between x2 x3 and x6 so if you do this in the undirected graph without the
在没有现代化步骤的无向图中
in the undirected graph without the modernization step and you get me the
modernization step and you get me the perspire first what are you going to do
首先先出汗，你将在图形中做什么尼克会成为什么样子
perspire first what are you going to do in the graph what Nick is going to be
in the graph what Nick is going to be introduced you remember in the simulator
介绍了您还记得在模拟器中是否需要连接邻居
introduced you remember in the simulator if you need to connect the neighbors
if you need to connect the neighbors right and whether the neighbors are 5 3
正确的，以及邻居是否是5 3＆6，所以从中将会丢失什么
right and whether the neighbors are 5 3 &amp; 6 so what is going to be missing from
&amp; 6 so what is going to be missing from the girls but somehow is not going to
女孩，但不知何故不能解释这里暗示的依赖性
the girls but somehow is not going to account for the dependence implied here
account for the dependence implied here x2 and x3 so the link between x2 x3 is
x2和x3，因此x2 x3之间的链接将会丢失
x2 and x3 so the link between x2 x3 is going to be missing is not going to be
going to be missing is not going to be there ok is the perfect 6 what do you do
好的是完美的6，您如何将X 2和X 5链接起来？
there ok is the perfect 6 what do you do you link X 2 and X 5 you see its
you link X 2 and X 5 you see its neighbors become what knows in the
邻居变成了无神的上帝所知道的东西，现在它确定你可以
neighbors become what knows in the undirected God now it sure you may
undirected God now it sure you may realize you're going to put this link
意识到你将把这个链接从3到5
realize you're going to put this link from 3 to 5
from 3 to 5 right now that you're going to eliminate
现在，您将要消除那表明您需要
right now that you're going to eliminate right there that says you need to
right there that says you need to connect there the neighbors and the
连接那里的邻居和5的邻居现在将是1 2
connect there the neighbors and the neighbors of 5 now going to be which 1 2
neighbors of 5 now going to be which 1 2 &amp; 3
＆3，这就是您获得23链接的方式
&amp; 3 and that's how you get the link of 23
and that's how you get the link of 23 in other ways the motorization comes
在其他方面，电动化来自正确的x6，并且事情没有进展
in other ways the motorization comes from x6 right and the thing is not going
from x6 right and the thing is not going to be around but there but now there is
周围，​​但是现在有一个依赖关系，您需要引入
to be around but there but now there is a dependency that you need to introduce
a dependency that you need to introduce between x2 x3 but to see here that
在x2 x3之间，但要在这里看到它们将丢失，因为您
between x2 x3 but to see here that they're going to be missing because you
they're going to be missing because you demoralize the parents of x6 okay so the
使x6的父母丧气，好吧，对不起，但是如果您这样做并且您做了
demoralize the parents of x6 okay so the sorry but if you do this and you do a
sorry but if you do this and you do a perfect 6 look that's where I was asking
完美的6外观，那是我肯定要问我的地方，显然你不会
perfect 6 look that's where I was asking me surely obviously you're not going to
me surely obviously you're not going to have a problem with the algorithm but if
该算法有问题，但是如果您要先消除过期
have a problem with the algorithm but if you want to eliminate expiring first
you want to eliminate expiring first that's when the problem appears so here
那是问题出现的时间，这就是您要使用的算法
that's when the problem appears so here is the algorithm you are going to you
is the algorithm you are going to you need to moralize the graph and then
需要道德化图，然后将其应用于有向图，以消除
need to moralize the graph and then apply this on directed graph eliminate
apply this on directed graph eliminate algo so does paralyze it to us for
算法也会使它瘫痪，成为永恒的有向图，并应用它
algo so does paralyze it to us for eternal directed graph and apply this
eternal directed graph and apply this algorithm that is truly best for graph
真正最适合图论的算法，您会做的任何事，这就是
algorithm that is truly best for graph theory do anything you know this is how
theory do anything you know this is how the algorithm is working in action for
例如，如果消除是
the algorithm is working in action for example if let's say the elimination is
example if let's say the elimination is eliminate so this was the dark lines of
消除，所以这是您将其与原始图相比较的暗线
eliminate so this was the dark lines of the original graph you marry this to
the original graph you marry this to this dotted line comes from organization
这条虚线来自组织，这条线来自于
this dotted line comes from organization and this line has come where this is
and this line has come where this is because you know you married the parents
因为你知道你嫁给了X 6的父母，所以这行是因为
because you know you married the parents of X 6 and this line comes because what
of X 6 and this line comes because what when you are ready to eliminate X 5 we
当您准备消除X 5时，我们需要更正其两个的标签
when you are ready to eliminate X 5 we need to correct its labels of their two
need to correct its labels of their two and three so two different origin one is
三个是两个不同的起源，一个是现代化，另一个是
and three so two different origin one is the modernization the other one is is
the modernization the other one is is coming by connecting so long comes
通过连接来连接很长时间基本上来自于此部分
coming by connecting so long comes basically from this part of the
basically from this part of the algorithm the other one comes from the
算法，另外一个来自无向图，三分钟
algorithm the other one comes from the undirected graph three minutes
好吧，接下来的事情是，现在人们真的已经看到了，所以我
all right the next thing is really now people really have seen it okay so I'm
people really have seen it okay so I'm going to stop there and then I'm going
要停在那里，然后我要换课，然后我要去
going to stop there and then I'm going to switch lecture and I'm going to go to
to switch lecture and I'm going to go to punish my computer do you see a mouse on
惩罚我的电脑，您是否在屏幕上看到鼠标
punish my computer do you see a mouse on the screen
所以我应该怎么做好，让我先把这东西拿出来
so what do I supposed to do okay let me remove this thing out first
remove this thing out first now people lost uh some of the computer
现在人们失去了一些计算机屏幕
now people lost uh some of the computer screen
好的，所以我们基本上要看如何
all right okay so we're going to basically see how
okay so we're going to basically see how slowly this positive factorization that
慢慢地，这种在无神的神中分布的积极因式分解
slowly this positive factorization that distributions in undirected God
distributions in undirected God okay and actually I'm going to come back
好的，实际上我将更严格地回到这个主题
okay and actually I'm going to come back to this topic sort of in a more rigorous
to this topic sort of in a more rigorous language maybe four or five lectures
语言大概四五堂课就可以了，但是现在我们要做
language maybe four or five lectures okay so but right now we're going to do
okay so but right now we're going to do sort of an intermediate easygoing
一种无向图的中间随和表示
sort of an intermediate easygoing presentation of undirected graphs and
presentation of undirected graphs and maybe next Thursday we'll discuss a
也许下周四，我们将讨论所谓的因素
maybe next Thursday we'll discuss a little bit about what's called factor
little bit about what's called factor graphs alright so we have seen this in
图还可以，所以我们已经详细讨论了这一点，
graphs alright so we have seen this in more detail we just discussed about
more detail we just discussed about directed graphs another name from the
有向图的有序图是马尔可夫随机场的另一个名字。
directed graphs another name from the raphe graphs is Markov random fields for
raphe graphs is Markov random fields for ghosts in in physics engineering etc you
物理工程等方面的幽灵，您必须阅读，对此有兴趣
ghosts in in physics engineering etc you know must read you be interested on this
know must read you be interested on this type of models people for example in
在社交网络中出现问题的人的模型类型
type of models people for example in social networks in in problems that
social networks in in problems that there is a causal relations they are
他们对贝叶斯网络有因果关系，但是
there is a causal relations they are interested in Bayesian networks but
interested in Bayesian networks but actually most algorithms but you know if
实际上大多数算法，但是您知道是否要对此进行操作
actually most algorithms but you know if you if you want to operate on this you
you if you want to operate on this you will transport with some other core most
将与其他一些核心一起运输，最有可能您知道一个无向图
will transport with some other core most probably you know an undirected graph
probably you know an undirected graph for the factor graph okay so it's not
对于因子图来说还可以，所以这不是像我们要让它们有所不同
for the factor graph okay so it's not like we're going to let them different
like we're going to let them different techniques for each graph but I'm just
每个图的技巧，但我只是说这是标准的操作方式
techniques for each graph but I'm just saying this is the standard way of doing
saying this is the standard way of doing things to tell in in engineering you
在工程学中要说的事情您知道对随机属性进行建模并
things to tell in in engineering you know modeling random properties and
know modeling random properties and things like that this is more in when
这样的事情更多是在您具有因果关系时
things like that this is more in when you have causality relation okay we
you have causality relation okay we mentioned one example that would like to
提到了一个想回到现在的例子，基本上
mentioned one example that would like to come back now to it okay so basically
come back now to it okay so basically you know our model so we have nodes
您知道我们的模型，所以我们的节点与以前完全一样，但是随机
you know our model so we have nodes exactly as before but there are random
exactly as before but there are random variables we have entities that describe
我们拥有描述基本独立关系的实体的变量，以及
variables we have entities that describe basically independent relations and
basically independent relations and there is no
没有对称性，但与方向性有关
there is no symmetry but has to do with directional
symmetry but has to do with directional arrows so there's a sense of think that
箭头，所以有一种感觉，你知道我是你的父母
arrows so there's a sense of think that you know I'm your parent here everyone
you know I'm your parent here everyone is the parent you know so the summation
是您知道的父代，所以a和C之间的总和就可以了
is the parent you know so the summation between a and C is equivalent okay there
between a and C is equivalent okay there is no directionality here and it comes
在这里没有方向性，但它却出现了，但独立性意识到了这一点
is no directionality here and it comes up but the independence realizes this
up but the independence realizes this very important one of the electric
非常重要的电动阀之一
very important one of the electric valves
valves they're basically got separation you
他们基本上是分开的，你知道想法，所以这是我的一个关系
they're basically got separation you know ideas so here is a one relation I
know ideas so here is a one relation I said that a and B are independent given
说a和B是独立的，给定两个T和D好的，那么发生的是
said that a and B are independent given two T and D okay so what happens is to
two T and D okay so what happens is to the conditioned on C and D and I claim
以C和D为条件，我声称a独立于B，因为每个
the conditioned on C and D and I claim that a is independent of B because every
that a is independent of B because every party from A to B has to pass through C
从A到B的一方必须经过C和D，所以如果我给C和D，则路径为
party from A to B has to pass through C and D so if I given C and D the path is
and D so if I given C and D the path is blocked in a completely graph theoretic
被完全图论的理论浪费所阻塞，换句话说，没有路径
blocked in a completely graph theoretic waste in other words there is no path
waste in other words there is no path from A to B that doesn't pass through
从A到B不会通过C和D的并集
from A to B that doesn't pass through see the union of C and D okay it's a
see the union of C and D okay it's a critical Hritik graph theoretic
关键的Hritik图理论算法，所以我们确实有这个
critical Hritik graph theoretic algorithm right so we do have this
algorithm right so we do have this explain a wasting we had with the torque
解释我们在定向中显示的扭矩独立性所造成的浪费
explain a wasting we had with the torque independence that we show in directed
independence that we show in directed graphical models so here you know if you
图形模型，因此在这里您知道是否应用beta小算法以及是否
graphical models so here you know if you apply the beta small algorithm and if
apply the beta small algorithm and if you have to pass through a path of knows
您必须经过一条我已经描述过的基本知识
you have to pass through a path of knows that I've described basically that
that I've described basically that immediately defines the conditional
立即定义此工艺的条件独立关系
immediately defines the conditional independence relations for this craft a
independence relations for this craft a very simple calculation if you have n
非常简单的计算，如果您有n个随机变量，那么让我们看看
very simple calculation if you have n random variables okay and let's see what
random variables okay and let's see what I'm doing is I'm completing all possible
我正在做的是完成所有可能的建立关系的方式
I'm doing is I'm completing all possible ways of coming up with relationships
ways of coming up with relationships that shake here between three random
可以在三个随机变量之间晃动，所以在这种情况下，
that shake here between three random variables okay so in this case the
variables okay so in this case the player on the variables are fully
变量上的播放器是完全独立的在这里
player on the variables are fully independent all right here this one
independent all right here this one connection or the connection etc and
连接或连接等，以及
如果我有n个随机变量并且它们是二进制的，让我们来考虑这种情况
independent all right here this one connection or the connection etc and
if I have n random variables and they're binary let's take this case
如果我有n个随机变量并且它们是二进制的，让我们来考虑这种情况
binary let's take this case naturally not binary this two shares
很自然，这两个份额不是二进制的，谢谢这是总数
naturally not binary this two shares thanks for what this is the total number
thanks for what this is the total number of undirected graphs because here mmm
无向图的原因，因为在这里mmm的底部也是我对2的要求。
of undirected graphs because here mmm the bottom also my claim is 2 to the
the bottom also my claim is 2 to the power n n minus 1 over 2 the distance
如果我必须知道，我的意思是距离nn减去2的1倍
power n n minus 1 over 2 the distance for what I mean if I have to knowledge
for what I mean if I have to knowledge there's no self connect to go they are
没有自我联系去，他们没有联系
there's no self connect to go they are not connected
not connected that's what are the two cups ok so the
那是两个杯子好吗，所以您可以获得的图形总数
that's what are the two cups ok so the total number of graphs that you can get
total number of graphs that you can get undirected graphs or the set of them
无向图或它们从变量集中的集合是2到幂M
undirected graphs or the set of them from the variables is 2 to the power M
from the variables is 2 to the power M times n minus 1 over 2m is because you
n减去1超过2m是因为您有印象笔记
times n minus 1 over 2m is because you have evernotes
have evernotes and every node can be connected with the
每个节点都可以与其他n减去1已知和2连接，因为
and every node can be connected with the other n minus 1 known and 2 because
other n minus 1 known and 2 because there is no directionality through you
通过您没有方向性，您必须知道重复计算
there is no directionality through you have to you know to double count
have to you know to double count basically the number of graphs
现在基本上是上帝代表您的图表数量
basically the number of graphs now which God basically represents your
now which God basically represents your problem based on a realization of random
基于随机变量实现的问题
problem based on a realization of random variables
variables what's the graph structure of the my
我的会话问题的图形结构是什么，我们将回到
what's the graph structure of the my session problem and we will come back to
session problem and we will come back to it way later in the course from history
从历史独立关系到后来的过程中
it way later in the course from history independence relations in undirected
independence relations in undirected graphs is what I described before
图是我之前描述的非常简单的东西，没有你不知道
graphs is what I described before extremely simple there is no you don't
extremely simple there is no you don't need to remember the rules
需要记住您所知道的规则，我们必须共同分享这些知识
need to remember the rules you know we have to share them heads and
you know we have to share them heads and tails or all of these things that we did
尾巴或我们所做的所有这些事情都可以直接将其绘制成图形
tails or all of these things that we did could directly graphs this is
could directly graphs this is independent of not given X B when every
当这组记录中的每个路径都记录结果时，与未给定的XB无关
independent of not given X B when every path from this set of notes the result
path from this set of notes the result of not just passed through the xB notes
不仅可以通过xB注释传递，还可以，所以基本上
of not just passed through the xB notes okay so basically the concept of
okay so basically the concept of conditional independence becomes a graph
条件独立成为图论概念好
conditional independence becomes a graph theoretic concept okay
theoretic concept okay it has nothing to do with any particular
它与我们所见过的任何特定的三角洲无关
it has nothing to do with any particular the Delta we have seen for directed
the Delta we have seen for directed graphs
图表
我想看看这个方程式并告诉我你知道的位置吗
the Delta we have seen for directed graphs
is this a position where I wants to look at this equation and telling me you know
我想看看这个方程式并告诉我你知道的位置吗
at this equation and telling me you know so basically what I say here we have two
所以基本上我在这里说的是，我们在图上有两个节点，我假设
so basically what I say here we have two nodes on the graph and I'm assuming that
nodes on the graph and I'm assuming that they're not connected via net so another
他们没有通过网络连接，所以另一个给一个没有连接的J是这个
they're not connected via net so another going give a no J not connected is this
going give a no J not connected is this equation based on my graph support the
基于我的图的方程式支持此条件独立性
equation based on my graph support the got this condition independence
got this condition independence condition is this correct if I and J are
如果I和J没有正确连接，则条件是正确的。
condition is this correct if I and J are not connected right every part from I to
not connected right every part from I to J has to go through what I steer J is
J必须经历我的指导J在那里，它们不是唯一的连接方式
J has to go through what I steer J is there they're not connected the only way
there they're not connected the only way to go is through the other node right
要经过另一个节点，就必须经过任何
to go is through the other node right you have to go through whatever the
you have to go through whatever the other nodes and immediately we know if
其他节点，我们立即知道其他节点是否像您一样给予我们
other nodes and immediately we know if the other nodes are given like you we
the other nodes are given like you we condition they're then given various
然后它们被赋予各种xixj必须独立的条件
condition they're then given various xixj have to be independent you see
我是说我们说对的夫妇，但这是独立的，如果给定XP
I mean the couple we said right but this is independent that if a given XP if
is independent that if a given XP if every part from here to there has to
从这里到那里的每个部分都必须经过它，因为XP
every part from here to there has to pass through it to be because XP would
pass through it to be because XP would block it so he heard if I and J don't
阻止它，所以他听说如果我和J不占优势，我可以声称他们
block it so he heard if I and J don't hold an edge I can claim that their
hold an edge I can claim that their condition independent given the rest of
给定其余节点，则条件独立，因为我唯一的方法是
condition independent given the rest of the nodes because the only way I can
the nodes because the only way I can work for my DJ is through the rest of
我的DJ的工作是通过弹出的其余节点进行的，因此
work for my DJ is through the rest of the nodes which that pop okay so the
the nodes which that pop okay so the addition is I am writing this as a
另外，我正在将其写为经过认证的通用药物
addition is I am writing this as a certified generic
如果您喜欢这是一个有条件的条件独立关系，但我不会
certified generic
if you like it's an eric conditional independence relation but I won't desk a
如果您喜欢这是一个有条件的条件独立关系，但我不会
independence relation but I won't desk a to motivate the concept that the joint
激发可以写出联合概率分布的概念
to motivate the concept that the joint probability distribution can be written
probability distribution can be written as a product or potential but each of
作为一种产品或潜力，但他们各自拒绝更好地单击“确定”，
as a product or potential but each of them is declined to better click OK and
them is declined to better click OK and so this relation or pretentious defined
因此，集团之间的这种关系或自命不凡的定义是一种
so this relation or pretentious defined over the clique is sort of a way to
over the clique is sort of a way to implicitly enforce the independence
隐式地执行您在那里看到的独立关系，所以
implicitly enforce the independence relation that you see up there okay so
relation that you see up there okay so let's see what I don't know when I go on
让我们看看我什么时候不知道，因为我们已经下巴了
let's see what I don't know when I go on this thing because we already have chin
this thing because we already have chin it okay so an example with some notes
没关系，所以有一些注释的例子，看看我们在这里有多少点击，所以
it okay so an example with some notes and see what clicks we have here so the
and see what clicks we have here so the this of the edges of the graph so the
图的边缘，所以头部的唯一连接是
this of the edges of the graph so the only connection of the head is between
only connection of the head is between x1 and x4 okay
x1和x4好的，所以这里有一个单击
x1 and x4 okay so there are this is a click alright one
so there are this is a click alright one click X 1 X 2 X 3 is another click
click X 1 X 2 X 3是另一个click expiry export是另一个希腊权利，
click X 1 X 2 X 3 is another click expiry export is another Greek right and
expiry export is another Greek right and so the maximal cliques place take care
所以最大派系的地方要照顾3号的大小，所以我会写成
so the maximal cliques place take care of size of size 3 so I will write the
of size of size 3 so I will write the Joint Distribution we write it as
联合分布我们将其写为在其上定义的势的乘积
Joint Distribution we write it as product of potentials defined over it's
product of potentials defined over it's much more click OK
点击确定实际上是您应该做的
much more click OK actually what you should do right as a
actually what you should do right as a result of the little exercise and maybe
小运动的结果，也许可以肯定，我们可以为您做些功课
result of the little exercise and maybe sure we can give you a little homework
sure we can give you a little homework problem is go through this all right
问题是可以通过一些简单的调试来解决所有问题，然后
problem is go through this all right with some simple tune-up and then
with some simple tune-up and then basically show the independence the
基本显示独立性我的条件独立性关系
basically show the independence the condition independence relation that I
condition independence relation that I mentioned before that victim how this
在那个受害者之前提到过，这怎么知道最大到X右边
mentioned before that victim how this knows come over maximal to X right
knows come over maximal to X right obviously they don't overlap and nothing
显然，它们不会重叠，并且没有任何东西可以冲洗有条件的垃圾
obviously they don't overlap and nothing flushes the refuse conditional
flushes the refuse conditional independence relations that we mentioned
我们之前提到的独立关系
independence relations that we mentioned before
before okay so Z's the normalization factor
好吧，Z是归一化因子，因为该电位不
okay so Z's the normalization factor because this potentials are not
because this potentials are not probabilities right they're just you
正确的概率，它们只是您知道的功能，但在某种意义上甚至
probabilities right they're just you know functions but in some sense even
know functions but in some sense even other probabilities they sort of the
其他概率，他们对所取的值进行排序，表示如何
other probabilities they sort of the values that they take Express how
values that they take Express how related power pairs or triplets Luce
相关的功率对或三元组Luce变量取决于多少
related power pairs or triplets Luce variables right depending how many
variables right depending how many variables you have on this earth so they
您在地球上拥有的变量，因此它们不是概率，而是实际
variables you have on this earth so they are not probabilities but the actually
are not probabilities but the actually captured the way the variables are
捕捉了变量相关的方式，他没有
captured the way the variables are correlated in the ground he didn't
correlated in the ground he didn't increase his mana
增加他的法力[鼓掌]
increase his mana [Applause]
[Applause] okay all right
好吧，所以我所做的就是
okay all right so what I have done it there is the
so what I have done it there is the knowledge don't form a clique because WC
知识不会形成集团，因为WC没有连接，所以如果我有这四个
knowledge don't form a clique because WC is not connected so if I have these four
is not connected so if I have these four variables I can write the joint
我可以将联合概率分布写为变量
variables I can write the joint probability distribution as the
probability distribution as the probability of T maximal cliques but R 1
T最大派系的概率，但R 1 xy和z XY和Z以及另一个wy
probability of T maximal cliques but R 1 x y and z XY and Z and another one wy in
x y and z XY and Z and another one wy in there okay Austin all right
奥斯汀，好吧，这就是我们所看到的组成
there okay Austin all right this is the composition that we see
this is the composition that we see there is not unique all right so
没有唯一的权利，所以有时候你知道你知道你可以
there is not unique all right so sometimes you know you you know you can
sometimes you know you you know you can manipulate it differently and come up
对其进行不同的处理，并提出各种表达方式
manipulate it differently and come up with some all the ways to express this
with some all the ways to express this discrete potential so this decomposition
离散电位，因此此分解不必是唯一的，但现在
discrete potential so this decomposition doesn't have to be unique but right now
doesn't have to be unique but right now that's not an issue because at the end
这不是问题，因为在一天结束时，您对
that's not an issue because at the end of the day you're interested on
of the day you're interested on joint distribution so let's try and do
联合分布，所以让我们尝试做一个简单的三个节点的例子
joint distribution so let's try and do one example of simple three nodes okay
one example of simple three nodes okay and stick this what we can represent
并坚持下去，我们可以用自己可以表示的方式来代表这一点，所以
and stick this what we can represent this in terms of put themselves okay so
this in terms of put themselves okay so one where it is I
我要去的地方我猜只有一个
one where it is I I'm gonna guess there is only enough
I'm gonna guess there is only enough separation in conditional independence
条件独立关系中的分离在这里给出了YX的踪迹
separation in conditional independence relation here the trace that given Y X
relation here the trace that given Y X and z are independent
和z是独立的，所以当我尝试强制执行此操作时，
and z are independent okay so when I try to enforce this and
okay so when I try to enforce this and see that this expression actually leads
看到这个表达式实际上导致了带有泄漏的分解。
see that this expression actually leads to decomposition of with leaks of the
to decomposition of with leaks of the Joint Distribution so what you see here
联合分布，所以您在此处看到的是x和y的P，而z等于
Joint Distribution so what you see here is P of x and y and z is equal to that
is P of x and y and z is equal to that so this equation that you see in the
因此，您在中间看到的这个等式证明食物是没有道理的
so this equation that you see in the middle you justify that food there's no
middle you justify that food there's no nothing assumption there but I simplify
那里没有任何假设，但我简化了，我说给定x和y的Z的P是P
nothing assumption there but I simplify and I say that P of Z given x and y is P
and I say that P of Z given x and y is P of Z given Y what can I use to do this I
给定Y的Z值，我该怎么做呢？我使用独立关系好吗
of Z given Y what can I use to do this I use the independence relation okay all
use the independence relation okay all right effectively what I can do is I can
我可以做的就是有效地将这些东西结合在一起
right effectively what I can do is I can combine those things together and this
combine those things together and this becomes the joint affection of Y and
成为Y的共同情感，这成为Z给定的条件
becomes the joint affection of Y and this becomes is the condition of Z given
this becomes is the condition of Z given Y so I can call really this my XY
是的，所以我可以称其为XY电位，因为那是一键操作，而我
Y so I can call really this my XY potential because that's one click and I
potential because that's one click and I can call this my Y Z potential that
可以将其称为来自此点击的我的YZ潜力
can call this my Y Z potential that comes from from this click interesting
comes from from this click interesting you know there is no way in general to
你知道一般没有办法写这个倡议的例子，但是你
you know there is no way in general to write this initiative an example but you
write this initiative an example but you cannot write this you cannot fertilize
不能写这个，你不能在力量上使这种分配受精
cannot write this you cannot fertilize this distribution in terms of power
this distribution in terms of power let's say conditional distributions to
假设要学习的条件分布或联合分布
let's say conditional distributions to learn or joint distribution so long it's
learn or joint distribution so long it's just not going to happen
只是不会发生，所以在这种情况下，您得到了一个
just not going to happen all right so in this case you get one
all right so in this case you get one joint distribution as one potential
联合分配是一种潜在的，另一种是有条件的，另一种是有条件的
joint distribution as one potential another one a conditional as the other
another one a conditional as the other potential and you know I can I mention
潜力，你知道我能提到这种分解不是唯一的
potential and you know I can I mention that this decomposition is not unique
that this decomposition is not unique it's just combining the P of Y would be
它只是将Y的P组合为Z逗号，YI可以用另一种形式编写
it's just combining the P of Y would be of Z comma Y I can write this in another
of Z comma Y I can write this in another factorization where the Y Z potential
YZ势成为y MZ和XY的结合的因式分解
factorization where the Y Z potential becomes the join of y MZ and the XY
becomes the join of y MZ and the XY potential becomes the conditional
势成为给定条件的条件，所以它不是唯一的
potential becomes the conditional effects given one so it's not unique
effects given one so it's not unique okay and as I said it doesn't really
好的，正如我所说的，这并不重要，不是说这比
okay and as I said it doesn't really matter it's not like this is better than
matter it's not like this is better than that you know they will do the same idea
你知道他们会做同样的想法，实际上我们甚至都不会去
that you know they will do the same idea and actually we will not even bother to
and actually we will not even bother to model visitors and say it is a joint or
给来访者建模，并说这是一个联合，或者是一个条件，不，这不是一些
model visitors and say it is a joint or it's a condition no it's not some
it's a condition no it's not some potential another potential define over
势力定义两个势力之间的另一个势力足以完成所有任务
potential another potential define over the two kliks enough to do the job all
the two kliks enough to do the job all right so the this is the first part of
对，所以这基本上是定理的第一部分，有两个三
right so the this is the first part of theorem basically and has two three
theorem basically and has two three versions from the theorem coming from
定理的版本来自统计力学
versions from the theorem coming from statistical mechanics really the
statistical mechanics really the homogeneity for theorem any distribution
定理的同质性任何分布都与无向图一致
homogeneity for theorem any distribution is consistent with an undirected graph
is consistent with an undirected graph and consistent means it satisfies this
并且一致意味着它满足此条件独立关系
and consistent means it satisfies this condition independence relationship
condition independence relationship supplied by the drop has the Joint
下降提供的具有联合分布的因式分解
supplied by the drop has the Joint Distribution the factorizes of the
Distribution the factorizes of the maximal cliques and looks like this okay
最大的派系，看起来像这样，此时的结构是任意的
maximal cliques and looks like this okay the structures at this point are any
the structures at this point are any pass the body functions of the variables
通过其变量中的变量的身体功能，好吧，我的意思是两只眼睛
pass the body functions of the variables in its clip okay is two eyes I mean
in its clip okay is two eyes I mean there's really nothing to put there but
真的没有什么可放的，而是从根本上追踪的
there's really nothing to put there but the so fundamentally traced
the so fundamentally traced any distribution satisfies this
提供的巴黎关系中的任何分布都满足此条件
any distribution satisfies this condition in the Paris relation supplied
condition in the Paris relation supplied by completely graph theoretic arguments
通过完全图论理论论证必须被授权为产品
by completely graph theoretic arguments has to be authorized in as the product
has to be authorized in as the product of potentials is potential the point
潜力是许多公众可以接受的重点，所以这就是
of potentials is potential the point over much public okay so that's the
over much public okay so that's the hammer strictly for theorem
严格为定理锤
好的，我的意思是，这基本上是同一版本的另一个版本
over much public okay so that's the hammer strictly for theorem
all right and and I mean this is basically another version of the same
好的，我的意思是，这基本上是同一版本的另一个版本
basically another version of the same theorem says if you learn is the common
定理说，如果学习是分布的共同点，民众就像
theorem says if you learn is the common of distributions the populace is like
of distributions the populace is like this and if you tour is the family of
如果您游览的是这个派系或满足的家庭
this and if you tour is the family of distributions or satisfies also
distributions or satisfies also conditional independence relations than
有条件的独立关系比你平等就好，所以你坐
conditional independence relations than you are equal to get to okay so you sit
you are equal to get to okay so you sit down and you write other personal
下来，然后您编写其他个人发行版，这些发行版占了所有
down and you write other personal distributions that account for all of
distributions that account for all of independence relations applied by this
由该无向图应用的独立关系，然后将所有
independence relations applied by this undirected graph and then you take all
undirected graph and then you take all distributions of the fertilizer in a gap
肥料在一个缝隙中的分布，那么两件事就是力量
distributions of the fertilizer in a gap then the two things are of the strength
可能很棒，您可以举例说明，然后告诉您这些形式
may be fabulous you do an example okay and tell you in which form these
and tell you in which form these potentials are coming is an
潜力来临时即兴演奏，因此请考虑
potentials are coming is an improvisation so consider that this have
improvisation so consider that this have arranged for example in in this building
安排在这个建筑权中，例如，它结束了，不是变量
arranged for example in in this building right and it's over no it's the variable
right and it's over no it's the variable that measures that say if the
该措施说，如果温度是原来的柯尔特全部
that measures that say if the temperature if it is original colt all
temperature if it is original colt all right the heating system is on or off so
正确的加热系统是开还是关，所以我们觉得这里有价值的练习
right the heating system is on or off so we felt that this valuable exercise here
we felt that this valuable exercise here is a binary plus one minus one just to
是二进制加一减一，只是为了使生活忙碌，这显然是
is a binary plus one minus one just to make life busy obviously this one is
make life busy obviously this one is called light you expect when you're
所谓的光，你期望当你将要被正确调用时，因为它们
called light you expect when you're going to be called right because they
going to be called right because they communicate through the world so there
通过世界交流，因此存在一种相关性，并且这种相关性
communicate through the world so there is a correlation and that correlation
is a correlation and that correlation sort of would try to capture it with the
可能会尝试以点击之类的潜力来捕获它
sort of would try to capture it with the potential that is the kind of the click
potential that is the kind of the click at higher next child and I am sure if
在较高的下一个孩子时，我确定您是否在基本的谨慎中知道
at higher next child and I am sure if you know in your elementary cautious
you know in your elementary cautious when you play with this type of mobiles
当您使用这种类型的手机时，您会说我要走最近的路
when you play with this type of mobiles you will say I'm going to take nearest
you will say I'm going to take nearest neighbors for interactions you know so
邻居，您知道在此图中的交互
neighbors for interactions you know so in this graph
in this graph obviously what's the size of the biggest
显然，此图中最大的诊所的规模是多少
obviously what's the size of the biggest clinics from this graph the way that you
clinics from this graph the way that you state
状态这是什么历史商店的大小
state is it what is the size of historic store
再次的原因是不知道这一点，因为记住一点就是你知道一个
and the reason again is not know this because remember a take is you know a
because remember a take is you know a maximal clique is every knowledge has to
最大的集团是每个知识都必须相互联系，无法被抓住
maximal clique is every knowledge has to be interconnected it cannot be caught
be interconnected it cannot be caught because this node and that node are not
因为这个节点和那个节点没有连接，所以怎么回事
because this node and that node are not connected so what's the matter sighs is
connected so what's the matter sighs is it great it's - okay so it's do so well
很好-好的，所以做得很好，然后我必须在这里发挥潜力
it great it's - okay so it's do so well then I have to work here with potentials
then I have to work here with potentials but involve basically two tables that
但基本上涉及两个表，有一些邻居可以
but involve basically two tables that there are sort of neighbors okay the
there are sort of neighbors okay the joint probability distribution and I
联合概率分布，我将介绍一些您知道的参数
joint probability distribution and I will introduce some parameters you know
will introduce some parameters you know is let's say whatever parameters
假设定义电位的参数未知
is let's say whatever parameters defining the potential are unknown in
defining the potential are unknown in general all right but I'm going to write
一般没事，但是我将其写为潜力的产物，
general all right but I'm going to write this as a product of potentials and
this as a product of potentials and remember the potentials need to be
记住潜力需要是积极的，因为当你把它们
remember the potentials need to be positive because when you put them
positive because when you put them together you need to give the
您需要一起给出概率分布和简单的方法
together you need to give the probability distribution and an easy way
probability distribution and an easy way to make them positive is to write them
使它们变得积极的是将它们写为e，具有某种能力，好吧，这是
to make them positive is to write them as e to some power okay this is sort of
as e to some power okay this is sort of a very typical of disposable type of
这是非常典型的一次性分配类型，因此我在这里写
a very typical of disposable type of distribution so here I am writing its
distribution so here I am writing its potential as e to the PI J that connects
电位e到连接节点XI和XJ的PI J的电位，所以我的电位是
potential as e to the PI J that connects nodes X I and X J so my potential is
nodes X I and X J so my potential is really not the price today is to e to
今天的价格真的不是等于e等于PI J的某个函数
really not the price today is to e to the theta equal to PI J some function
the theta equal to PI J some function because that way the function can be
因为那样函数可以是正的也可以是负的
because that way the function can be positive or negative but e to the T PI J
positive or negative but e to the T PI J will always be positive
永远是积极的，我基本上只是在制定公式，所以我
will always be positive I'm just very formulating basically so I
I'm just very formulating basically so I don't have to worry about something
不必担心负面的影响，好吧，另一个好处是
don't have to worry about something being negative okay another advantage is
being negative okay another advantage is if you write this as product of this
如果您将此代码编写为此指数函数的乘积
if you write this as product of this exponential function when you might have
exponential function when you might have to put them together you know based on
将它们放在一起，您会基于我们之前在这里讨论的内容而了解到
to put them together you know based on that here we discussed before if you're
that here we discussed before if you're going to get e to the sum of the theta J
将要获得e到theta J的总和的定义是在
going to get e to the sum of the theta J is defined over all the edges of the
is defined over all the edges of the graph
图形
好的，这是一个归一化因子，这意味着
is defined over all the edges of the graph
okay all right and this is a normalization factor which means this
好的，这是一个归一化因子，这意味着
normalization factor which means this into the summation of this you're going
总结一下，您将必须采样所有可能的值
into the summation of this you're going to have to sample all possible values of
to have to sample all possible values of x our next area all right and after this
x我们的下一个区域可以，在此之后，希望您可能需要这样做
x our next area all right and after this and hopefully you may have to do it by
and hopefully you may have to do it by market show because this step is where
市场展示，因为这一步是所有物理的发展方向，因此，如果您想
market show because this step is where all the physics is coming so if you want
all the physics is coming so if you want to do statistical mechanics or compute
做统计机制或计算有趣的属性
to do statistical mechanics or compute interesting properties you mean
interesting properties you mean everything has to go through this
一切都必须经过这个归一化因子，但是
everything has to go through this normalization factor but sort of
normalization factor but sort of responds well to free energy for the
对系统的自由能反应良好，您会注意到它的
responds well to free energy for the system okay and you notice it's
system okay and you notice it's complicated because estimation of the
很复杂，因为估算的估算还可以，那么如何精确地进行估算
complicated because estimation of the estimation alright so how exactly do
estimation alright so how exactly do this is to be seen all right so this is
这是可以看到的，所以这是一堆马来分布，好吧，
this is to be seen all right so this is a bunch maleic distribution okay and
a bunch maleic distribution okay and there's nothing here
这里什么都没有
现在，先生，我们从海豚开始的上一个例子将赏金
a bunch maleic distribution okay and there's nothing here
now sir the previous example we started with the dolphin will bounty the
现在，先生，我们从海豚开始的上一个例子将赏金
with the dolphin will bounty the authorization of the distribution over
现在授权在地面上进行分配，我们想一路过关斩将
authorization of the distribution over the ground now suppose we go all the way
the ground now suppose we go all the way around and somebody gives you a
周围，​​有人给你分解定义了
around and somebody gives you a factorization defining over the sets of
factorization defining over the sets of know how do you specify an undirected
知道您如何基本上基于基础工作来指定无向图
know how do you specify an undirected graph basically that the based work
graph basically that the based work authorization the other problem is so
授权另一个问题是，它们可能但可能会产生一些影响
authorization the other problem is so they might but be effects is some
they might but be effects is some function of X 1 X 2 X 5 times the
X 1 X 2 X的功能是X 4 X 3和X 25的功能的五倍
function of X 1 X 2 X 5 times the function of X 4 X 3 and X 25 how do you
function of X 4 X 3 and X 25 how do you make it go well the idea is very simple
让它顺利进行，这个想法非常简单，现在必须要做的是
make it go well the idea is very simple right this they have to be now is
right this they have to be now is corresponding to maximal cliques so what
与最大派系相对应，所以您需要做的是全部拿走
corresponding to maximal cliques so what you need to do is you need to take all
you need to do is you need to take all the nodes to find Cyrus pretentious and
找到Cyrus的自命不凡和收藏家的节点，当您完成时
the nodes to find Cyrus pretentious and collector and when you're finished
collector and when you're finished that's basically your undirected graph
那基本上就是你的无向图，好吧，别无选择，因为
that's basically your undirected graph ok there is no other way around because
ok there is no other way around because that's the only way that will allow you
这是唯一可以让您进行因式分解的方法
that's the only way that will allow you to have a factorization that basically
to have a factorization that basically looks in this ball
看着这个球
好的
to have a factorization that basically looks in this ball
all right
所以这是因为因为与独立
so the this comes to be because because just to do with the independent
just to do with the independent relations but I didn't have to tell you
关系，但我不必告诉您有关阿尔加（Algar）最大的一口井的信息
relations but I didn't have to tell you much about the biggest well Algar it
much about the biggest well Algar it right because if you want to share that
正确，因为如果您想共享X 1和X取决于X 5给定X 2
right because if you want to share that X 1 and X is to depend of X 5 given X 2
X 1 and X is to depend of X 5 given X 2 and and explore the only thing you have
并探索您要做的唯一一件事就是选择一条从1到5的路径
and and explore the only thing you have to do is take a path from 1 to 5 and it
to do is take a path from 1 to 5 and it has to go through 2 &amp; 4 then the path is
必须经过2和4，然后路径被阻塞
has to go through 2 &amp; 4 then the path is blocked
blocked alright so you can use purely basically
好吧，所以如果可以使用，您可以使用纯粹的可达性条件
alright so you can use purely basically reachability conditions if you can use
reachability conditions if you can use its with a set of nodes the one set of
它与一组节点，一组节点和另一组通过绕过
its with a set of nodes the one set of nodes and other set by bypassing the
nodes and other set by bypassing the evidence then basically the condition
那么基本上没有条件独立性关系的证据
evidence then basically the condition independence relation will not be born
independence relation will not be born okay
好的
所以这个预防台的名字是什么，所以你知道，因为我们有
independence relation will not be born okay
so what's the name of this prevention table plate so you know because we have
所以这个预防台的名字是什么，所以你知道，因为我们有
table plate so you know because we have their condition distributions now you
他们的条件分布现在你知道如果我写这是相同的例子
their condition distributions now you know if I write this is the same example
know if I write this is the same example that we had before if I write this in
如果我用潜力来写这些，这些是我们以前所拥有的
that we had before if I write this in terms of potentials these potentials of
terms of potentials these potentials of two nodes two variables two variables
两个节点两个变量两个变量两个然后三个这不是
two nodes two variables two variables two then three this are not
two then three this are not probabilities okay and they express
概率还可以，它们表示变量之间的相关性，因此
probabilities okay and they express correlations between variables so
correlations between variables so example you see the anthem let's like
例如，您看到了国歌，就像这样，是离散变量，您可以看到吗
example you see the anthem let's like this are discrete variables can you see
this are discrete variables can you see an element there that is very small
那里的一个很小的元素意味着特定的变量集
an element there that is very small means the particular set of variables
means the particular set of variables are not correlated with each other but
彼此不相关，但是许多P可能是某种东西
are not correlated with each other but many P potentially it's something
many P potentially it's something computationally we need to worry because
在计算上，我们需要担心，因为这些因素没有被归一化，您可能会
computationally we need to worry because this factors are not normalized you may
this factors are not normalized you may have a problem when you do computation
在进行计算并影响共享参数时会遇到问题
have a problem when you do computation and influence that share parameters
and influence that share parameters because maybe this potential here is way
因为也许这里的潜力远比那高得多
because maybe this potential here is way at much higher values than that
at much higher values than that potential there that doesn't imply that
潜力，但这并不意味着该值基本上是性X
potential there that doesn't imply that the value were sexual X still basically
the value were sexual X still basically dominate the distribution simply this
仅仅因为发生这种情况就可以控制分布，因为您已经对其进行了归一化
dominate the distribution simply this happens because you have a normalize it
happens because you have a normalize it so you need to be careful when you do
因此在进行推断时需要小心，因为这可能是
so you need to be careful when you do inference because this terms may be
inference because this terms may be completely honest in the calculation
在计算中完全诚实，因为它们不太可能
completely honest in the calculation because they are not probabilities okay
because they are not probabilities okay in some sense this can be a problem you
从某种意义上说，这可能是一个问题，您要知道所有任务是什么
in some sense this can be a problem you know depending what the task is from all
know depending what the task is from all locations you may want to take advantage
您可能想利用的位置
locations you may want to take advantage of that
好吧，最无名的问题正好适合这种无向的概念
all right so the the most famous problem that fits in this concept of undirected
that fits in this concept of undirected graphical models is the Ising model for
图形化模型是针对那些正在学习基础课程的人的Ising模型
graphical models is the Ising model for those who have taking elementary courses
those who have taking elementary courses in physics this is University model
在物理学中，这是大学模型，提出了问题，她得到了
in physics this is University model where the matter was raised she got a
where the matter was raised she got a plus minus 1 so this your typical run
加减1，所以这是您通常会遇到的问题，但实际上是
plus minus 1 so this your typical run with this problem but actually as
with this problem but actually as trivial as this problem looks like right
这个问题看起来很对，这也是最困难的问题之一
trivial as this problem looks like right is also one of the most difficult
is also one of the most difficult problems to do especially in two and
特别是在二维和三维中要做的任何人都认为有问题
problems to do especially in two and three dimensions anybody that thinks
three dimensions anybody that thinks this chapter a problem you know the I
这章是你知道的一个问题，我的教科书基本上写了几百本
this chapter a problem you know the I textbooks basically written of hundreds
textbooks basically written of hundreds of pages that are discuss about this
讨论此问题的页面数是
of pages that are discuss about this problem and it is
problem and it is Shanta file a good test case for
Shanta提出了一个很好的测试案例来检查他们实际穿着的关系
Shanta file a good test case for checking relationship actually they wore
checking relationship actually they wore okay
好吧，让我们讨论一下，因为她有
okay and so let's discuss it because she has
and so let's discuss it because she has to do a lot with statistical mechanics
在统计力学上做很多事情，这是一个大实验
to do a lot with statistical mechanics this is in one big experiment can be
this is in one big experiment can be plus minus one and when you need to
加减一，当您需要捕获Ising模型时，您需要
plus minus one and when you need to capture of the Ising model is you need
capture of the Ising model is you need to capture sort of correlations between
捕获邻居之间的某种相关性，如果这是加一，
to capture sort of correlations between neighbors so if this is plus one you
neighbors so if this is plus one you know in thesis you say spin up for
在论文中知道你说例如在量子力学中自旋，所以如果这
know in thesis you say spin up for example in quantum mechanics so if this
example in quantum mechanics so if this is plus one then the neighbors tend to
是加一，那么邻居往往是加一，所以相应的身体是
is plus one then the neighbors tend to be plus one so the corresponding body is
be plus one so the corresponding body is that of the potential forgetting at
潜在的遗忘至少加上一个机会的天空
that of the potential forgetting at least plus one the sky of chance of
least plus one the sky of chance of getting this plus one in higher transfer
得到这个加一个更高的转移叫喊这个加一个和这张桌子
getting this plus one in higher transfer yelling this plus one and this table
yelling this plus one and this table step also look to represent that not in
步骤还试图表示它不是在概率的上下文中，而是
step also look to represent that not in the context of probabilities but
the context of probabilities but certainly in the context you know you
当然，在上下文中，您知道在上下文中，您知道
certainly in the context you know you know in the context of
你知道潜力，所以你可以在这里看到例如，如果这是负一
you know the potential so you can see here for example if this is minus one
here for example if this is minus one the probability of xn minus 1 B minus 1
xn减去1 B减去1的概率我是说，所以概率无除法
the probability of xn minus 1 B minus 1 I mean so the probability is no divide
I mean so the probability is no divide of the prevention is much higher than
预防的价值远高于完成价值的可能性
of the prevention is much higher than the probability of done the value of
the probability of done the value of excitements ought to be point two okay
激动应该是第二点好，我必须纠正自己，这是一个
excitements ought to be point two okay again I have to correct myself there's a
again I have to correct myself there's a lot probabilities then you notice they
很多概率，那么您会发现它们基本上不会在任何方向上相加
lot probabilities then you notice they don't sum up basically in any direction
don't sum up basically in any direction you see them if you want so if you write
如果愿意，您会看到他们，如果您将此联合发行版作为产品编写
you see them if you want so if you write this joint distribution as the product
this joint distribution as the product of potential functions of the form e to
形式e到负Tate的潜在函数的确定该产品将导致
of potential functions of the form e to the minus Tate ok this product will lead
the minus Tate ok this product will lead to estimation of the potential and this
估计潜力，这基本上就是您的哈密顿量
to estimation of the potential and this is basically your Hamiltonian for the
is basically your Hamiltonian for the system this is the energy of the system
系统，这是系统的能量，是能量的总和
system this is the energy of the system which is the summation of the energy
which is the summation of the energy storage click so in lots of problems in
存储单击，因此在无向的图形模型中不会出现很多问题
storage click so in lots of problems in in in undirected graphical models not
in in undirected graphical models not just in the Ising model but all of them
只是在伊辛模型中，但是所有这些实际上都是从您的潜力开始的
just in the Ising model but all of them actually starting with potentials you
actually starting with potentials you know what to start this with an energy
知道如何从能量函数开始，然后按e到减号旋钮
know what to start this with an energy function and then e to the minus knob
function and then e to the minus knob basically will give you the potential
基本上会给您很多潜在的潜力，您会看到
basically will give you the potential all right so much times you will see
all right so much times you will see people pasta mating directly the energy
人们将意大利面直接与能量交配过点击，然后
people pasta mating directly the energy over clicked all right and the
over clicked all right and the corresponding distribution would be a
相应的分布将是玻尔兹曼分布的减少
corresponding distribution would be a Boltzmann distribution reduce
Boltzmann distribution reduce distribution e to the minus 8 okay and
分配e到负8，好吧，如果你想参加聚会，你可以
distribution e to the minus 8 okay and if you want to make it party you can
if you want to make it party you can introduce temperature effects of things
引入诸如此类的温度效应，但现在没有兴趣
introduce temperature effects of things like that but of no interest right now
好的，所以这次讨论的是Boltzmann分布
okay so this discuss was the Boltzmann distribution all right
distribution all right what's the matter fluently remind me
这是怎么回事，让我清楚地想起了什么是马尔可夫毯子，
what's the matter fluently remind me what a Markov blanket in general for a
what a Markov blanket in general for a dialectic lab for example what was the
例如辩证实验室的定义是什么
dialectic lab for example what was the definition
所以是父母，比较之后，这个想法基本上就被推向了市场
so it was the parents and the comparison the idea was given the market basically
the idea was given the market basically the notes independent of anything else
注释独立于图形中的其他任何内容，所以在无向中
the notes independent of anything else in the graph alright so in in undirected
in the graph alright so in in undirected graphs if you want to think what the
图形，如果您想考虑什么是马尔可夫毯子，那是非常极端的
graphs if you want to think what the Markov blanket is it is extremely
Markov blanket is it is extremely trivial because the Markov blanket is
这是微不足道的，因为马尔可夫毯子实际上是该节点的邻居，因为
trivial because the Markov blanket is really the neighbors of the node because
really the neighbors of the node because if you given the neighbors there's no
如果你给邻居，就别无选择，因为
if you given the neighbors there's no way to go anywhere else because all
way to go anywhere else because all paths will be blocked okay so the Markov
路径将被阻止，所以无向图的马尔可夫毯是
paths will be blocked okay so the Markov blanket for an undirected graph is the
blanket for an undirected graph is the the neighbors of the nodes
节点的邻居
好的
blanket for an undirected graph is the the neighbors of the nodes
okay
所以您知道当我们在讨论记录图时，我们会发布一些
so you know when we were discussing about the record graphs we post some
about the record graphs we post some sort of trivial inference problem so if
琐碎的推理问题，因此，例如，如果您想要一个
sort of trivial inference problem so if you want for example so you have a
you want for example so you have a matching notes here by the tray this is
托盘在这里匹配笔记，这是X太热或太冷的问题
matching notes here by the tray this is the problem with X being hot or cold you
the problem with X being hot or cold you know different rooms and of course and
知道不同的房间，当然，这些是房间里的温度
know different rooms and of course and these are the temperatures in in its
these are the temperatures in in its room if you want to find given some
房间如果您想找到给定的证据，您将不会发现此条件
room if you want to find given some evidence you won't find this conditional
evidence you won't find this conditional distribution where the rest of the
基本上消除了其余六分位数的分布
distribution where the rest of the volume of sixes are eliminated basically
volume of sixes are eliminated basically what you need to do is this you can
您需要做的是，您可以像这样编写分子，并且
what you need to do is this you can write the numerator like that and the
write the numerator like that and the denominator of this thing stuff over a
这个东西的分母在可能的XJ束上填充，但在这种情况下
denominator of this thing stuff over a possible bunch of XJ but in this case
possible bunch of XJ but in this case take values minus 1 and 1 and the way
取值减去1和1，并且您处理证据的方式几乎相同
take values minus 1 and 1 and the way you handle evidence is sort of identical
you handle evidence is sort of identical with a way you handle evident in the
以一种方式处理有向图中的明显值，这样您就可以知道
with a way you handle evident in the directed graph so you can you know so on
directed graph so you can you know so on the denominator here you have the joint
分母在这里是XJ与J类型的证据的联合
the denominator here you have the joint of XJ with the evidence of type J
of XJ with the evidence of type J successively if this expression is
如果此表达式正确编写，则为连续求和
successively if this expression is written correctly this is the summation
written correctly this is the summation of over X bar the most accept XK but now
超过X条的人最接受XK，但现在通常乘以
of over X bar the most accept XK but now this usually multiplied by the Joint
this usually multiplied by the Joint Distribution with the evidence functions
带有证据的分发功能将在第二天跨越社会底层
Distribution with the evidence functions to cross the bottom of society next day
to cross the bottom of society next day to take this fat body
保持这个肥胖的身体好，所以没有什么不同
to take this fat body okay so there's nothing again different
okay so there's nothing again different from before the only difference is that
与之前相比，唯一的区别是这只手腕在这方面
from before the only difference is that this wrist briefly in terms of this
this wrist briefly in terms of this potentials 11 conditional distribution
势11条件分布，所以代数基本上是
potentials 11 conditional distribution so the algebra is basically sort of
so the algebra is basically sort of identical
完全相同的
好吧，我们现在怎么能停下来呢，你知道我们做了很多事情
so the algebra is basically sort of identical
all right how do we cannot stop now you know we did lots of things about
好吧，我们现在怎么能停下来呢，你知道我们做了很多事情
you know we did lots of things about directed graphs if you don't want to
有向图（如果您不想使用有向图）
directed graphs if you don't want to work with directed graphs how do you
work with directed graphs how do you respond to undirected graphs so let's
响应无向图，所以让我们看一下关节
respond to undirected graphs so let's look at the let's look at the joint
look at the let's look at the joint probability distribution so x1 x2 x3
概率分布，因此x1 x2 x3没有乘积右下历史记录部分
probability distribution so x1 x2 x3 have no product next right history part
have no product next right history part so we get something I got alright so
所以我们得到了我没事的东西，因此基于此和思考
so we get something I got alright so that is based on on this and thinking
that is based on on this and thinking what the undirected graph is going to
无向图将是什么样的，最大集团是什么
what the undirected graph is going to look like what is the maximum clique
look like what is the maximum clique that I need to have in the problem to
我需要在问题中正确表示
that I need to have in the problem to represent correctly that the
represent correctly that the characterization what should i what is
表征我该怎么做才能最大点击
characterization what should i what is the maximum click on it you have to
the maximum click on it you have to represent it
代表它
但这有X 1 X 2 X 3 X 4
the maximum click on it you have to represent it
but this has X 1 X 2 X 3 X 4
正确，因为出口取决于X产品的解释，就像退货一样
right because export depends on X products to explain so like a return
products to explain so like a return here that involves basically variables
这里基本上涉及变量，那么我最大的派系是什么
here that involves basically variables so what is the maximum clique that I
so what is the maximum clique that I expect to send the equivalent undirected
期望发送等价的无向图，但是如何从中得到四个
expect to send the equivalent undirected graph for but how can you get four from
graph for but how can you get four from this graph the only you can way you can
此图是您唯一可以使Cortez道德化的方法，因此
this graph the only you can way you can get Cortez moralization all right so
get Cortez moralization all right so basically you have to marry this balance
基本上，你必须嫁给这个平衡，你必须嫁给他们必须回应
basically you have to marry this balance you have to marry response they have to
you have to marry response they have to marry this product and this basically
嫁给这个产品，这基本上会给你一个派系，那就是
marry this product and this basically will give you a clique that is the
will give you a clique that is the maximum clique that reporter for so
实际上，在这种特殊情况下，记者实际上是最大的团体
maximum clique that reporter for so actually in this particular case right I
actually in this particular case right I can write this is only one potential
可以写这只是一个潜力，因为实际上只有一个最大值
can write this is only one potential because really there's only one maximum
because really there's only one maximum clique that involves four four notes I
涉及四个四个音符的集团我可以写业务尝试X 1 X 2 X之一
clique that involves four four notes I can write business try one of X 1 X 2 X
can write business try one of X 1 X 2 X 3 X 4 okay
3 X 4好的，如果您尝试包括在内的力量
3 X 4 okay the including strength if you try to
the including strength if you try to write the total prob in with more of the
用正确提及的更多术语写出总概率，这样您将获得
write the total prob in with more of the terms it's mention right so you will get
terms it's mention right so you will get some results but in reality you will
一些结果，但实际上您将永远无法精确建模
some results but in reality you will never be able to exactly model a
never be able to exactly model a distribution of a crisis this way the
这样分配危机的唯一方法是
distribution of a crisis this way the only way you can do this is by having a
only way you can do this is by having a maximal clique that has all four nodes
具有所有四个节点的最大集团，这个杂色只能是它们中的一个
maximal clique that has all four nodes and this much motley can only be of they
and this much motley can only be of they if you moralized the dialectic block
如果你把辩证法道德化，好吧，我想我会回到
if you moralized the dialectic block okay I think I'm going to go back to
okay I think I'm going to go back to show you some cases of directed graphs
向您展示一些有向图的情况，但是您无法提出
show you some cases of directed graphs but there is no way you can come up with
but there is no way you can come up with an equivalent undirected graph but right
一个等效的无向图，但是现在对于这个问题，您只是瘫痪了
an equivalent undirected graph but right now for this problem you just paralyze
now for this problem you just paralyze the parent and Verity okay so so here's
父母和Verity可以，所以如果有这个，这是另一个例子
the parent and Verity okay so so here's another example if you have this
another example if you have this directed graph
有向图
PF下一个具有平衡，即给定x1 x 4p f x3没有父级且
another example if you have this directed graph
PF next one has the balance the effects the given x1 x 4p f x3 has no parent and
PF下一个具有平衡，即给定x1 x 4p f x3没有父级且
the given x1 x 4p f x3 has no parent and then explore given x2 and x3 okay so so
然后探索给定的x2和x3好，所以你在这里注意到你有我的数字2 3
then explore given x2 and x3 okay so so you notice here you have my numbers 2 3
you notice here you have my numbers 2 3 &amp; 4
＆4好吧2 3＆4所以我还是
and obviously to get 2 3 &amp; 4 you have to moralize you have to marry the parents 2
有一个涉及2 3＆4的集团，显然要获得2 3＆4，您必须
道德化你必须嫁给父母2＆3，这是潜在的机会
and obviously to get 2 3 &amp; 4 you have to moralize you have to marry the parents 2
moralize you have to marry the parents 2 &amp; 3 and this is the line here potential
道德化你必须嫁给父母2＆3，这是潜在的机会
&amp; 3 and this is the line here potential notice because if I say I'm going to
注意，因为如果我说我将有潜力2 3＆4
notice because if I say I'm going to have a potential 2 3 &amp; 4
have a potential 2 3 &amp; 4 in that potential I can take actually
在这种潜力下，我可以实际利用Experion的这种可能性
in that potential I can take actually this probability of Experion make it
this probability of Experion make it popular prevent itself alright so if you
流行防止自己好吧，所以如果你想从左到右我
popular prevent itself alright so if you want to go from the left to the right I
want to go from the left to the right I can combine P of X 3 with the
可以将X 3的P与X 4 X 2 8 3的概率结合起来并定义
can combine P of X 3 with the probability of X 4 X 2 8 3 and define
probability of X 4 X 2 8 3 and define this potential and again because X 1 and
这种潜力又一次是因为X 1和X 2是我可以放入的两个节点的派系
this potential and again because X 1 and X 2 is a clique of two nodes I can put
X 2 is a clique of two nodes I can put these things together as another
这些东西一起作为另一个潜力，所以我想X 1和X 2这样
these things together as another potential so I want to of X 1 and X 2 so
potential so I want to of X 1 and X 2 so again you have potential to note and
再次，您有潜力要注意，另一个有三个节点的潜力，
again you have potential to note and another potential with three nodes and
another potential with three nodes and this problem before now belongs to non
这个问题以前属于非潜在问题，另一个是任何问题
this problem before now belongs to non potential and another is that any issue
我的意思是显然，您期望的是，如果您认为此点击是否来自
I mean obviously you expect I mean if you think if this clicks are coming from
you think if this clicks are coming from the wave behind were supported late and
后面的浪潮支撑得很晚，我们在这里带了一堆，
the wave behind were supported late and we take a bunch of them here and the
we take a bunch of them here and the boss of them
他们的老板，邻居，显然他们将成为
boss of them neighbors obviously they're going to be
neighbors obviously they're going to be staring some know if they don't say
盯着一些人知道他们是否不说基本没有必要做
staring some know if they don't say basically there is no point of doing a
basically there is no point of doing a methodology because the problem becomes
方法论，因为问题变得微不足道，所以事实是
methodology because the problem becomes trivial so the fact that there is no
trivial so the fact that there is no trick here is not an issue you know this
这不是问题，您知道这是此类问题中的典型问题，因此
trick here is not an issue you know this is typical in this sort of problems so
is typical in this sort of problems so let's look actually again for converting
让我们再来看一次将a直接转换为无向图的过程，
let's look actually again for converting a directly to an undirected graph so
a directly to an undirected graph so what I have seven nodes this is the
我有七个节点，这是有向图的因式分解，
what I have seven nodes this is the factorization for the directed graph and
factorization for the directed graph and what I have done is this conditional
我所做的是我写下的条件分布
what I have done is this conditional distributions I have written down as a
distributions I have written down as a product of joint distributions divided
联合分布除以边际的乘积，如果仔细看
product of joint distributions divided by marginals and if you look carefully
by marginals and if you look carefully of this expressions you will see that on
在这些表达式中，您将看到在分子上我拥有所有乘积
of this expressions you will see that on the numerator I have products of all
the numerator I have products of all right divide each of the progress of
右划分您在此处看到的点击交叉路口的每个进度
right divide each of the progress of click intersections you see here there
click intersections you see here there is x1 x3 all right
是x1 x3可以提取3，所以这个游戏基本上是
is x1 x3 all right extract 3 so this play is basically the
extract 3 so this play is basically the intersection of the two clicks of course
当然，两次点击的相交点最高的一棵树在另一个象限中
intersection of the two clicks of course tallest tree in quadrants another
tallest tree in quadrants another intersection there and similarly for the
相交，点击次数也一样4 5 4 6 4 7
intersection there and similarly for the clicks 4 5 4 6 4 7
clicks 4 5 4 6 4 7 right you have these intersections later
对，以后我们发展每个人的基本原理时，您会遇到这些交叉点
right you have these intersections later when we develop everybody's basically
when we develop everybody's basically for influence on general graphs we will
为了影响一般图表，我们将尝试利用这些图表的优势
for influence on general graphs we will try to take advantage on how these
try to take advantage on how these cliques communicate with each other so
集团之间相互交流，所以这种想法将是
cliques communicate with each other so this is sort of this idea will be
this is sort of this idea will be extended all right so this the trivial
扩展了所有的权利，所以这个琐碎的例子我不认为这是一个马尔可夫
extended all right so this the trivial example I don't think it's a Markov
example I don't think it's a Markov chain basically so you know again I
基本上是连锁的，所以您再次知道，我将其结合到潜能上，每个
chain basically so you know again I combine this to on potential and each of
combine this to on potential and each of the other conditional distributions two
其他条件分布两种其他可能性偶尔什么也没有
the other conditional distributions two other potentials occasional nothing
other potentials occasional nothing fancy so here you can remove all the
花式的，所以在这里您可以删除所有箭头，并基本上将此图制作为
fancy so here you can remove all the arrows and make basically this graph to
arrows and make basically this graph to have the same identical independence
具有与直接图形相同的独立关系，即您
have the same identical independence relations as to direct graph that you
relations as to direct graph that you see on the top so what I have here is I
在顶部看到，所以我在这里有另一个直接III和直接III
see on the top so what I have here is I have another direct III and direct III
have another direct III and direct III and the pol III okay and so can you
和POL III好，所以您能提醒我
and the pol III okay and so can you remind me what's the definition of an
remind me what's the definition of an undirected three obviously some directed
无向三显然是有向的，使无向图为三
undirected three obviously some directed what makes an undirected graph a three
它表示从该路径到任意一对节点之间的平均单个路径
it says the average a single path between any pair of nodes the way from
between any pair of nodes the way from here to there this is the only path to
从这里到那里，这是从这里到那里的唯一路径
here to there this is the only path to go from here to there there's only one
go from here to there there's only one path okay which is two three
路径还可以，是两个三
所以在大胆的环境中，有一个红色的节点让我们在这里和其他每个地方都说这个旋钮
go from here to there there's only one path okay which is two three
so in audacity there is a red node let's say this knob here and every other
所以在大胆的环境中，有一个红色的节点让我们在这里和其他每个地方都说这个旋钮
say this knob here and every other noxious how many parts only Ron
有害的只有罗恩（Ron）有多少部分，那么导演的关系是什么
noxious how many parts only Ron so what's the relation of a directed
so what's the relation of a directed three you think around the elected three
三选民，三思而后行，您还记得-因为居家权
three you think around the elected three you remember that - because home right a
you remember that - because home right a directive 3 - on directory we have to do
指令3-在目录上，我们必须首先执行电离过程
directive 3 - on directory we have to do first what process ionization so
first what process ionization so intensified demonization in the
目录中的强化妖魔化没有任何反应
intensified demonization in the directory nothing happened
directory nothing happened ok so basically because there's no
好的，基本上是因为没有动员发生，而是在3 a
ok so basically because there's no mobilization has happened but in 3 a
mobilization has happened but in 3 a purity is like a directory but nodes can
纯净性就像一个目录，但是节点可以具有多个功能，那么
purity is like a directory but nodes can have more than one power so what will
have more than one power so what will happen when I transform a 23 to an
当我将23转换为无向3时发生
happen when I transform a 23 to an undirected 3
例如，要解决这个问题，如果我能做到这一点，我会把它留得很好
so for example to make this around I left it well if I can make it this
left it well if I can make it this another mr. Pony three rights if I
另一位先生如果我想使其成为无向图，则小马拥有三项权利
another mr. Pony three rights if I wanted to make it an undirected graph
wanted to make it an undirected graph what is gonna happen here you will
这里会发生什么，您将与父母建立联系，如果您与父母建立联系，
what is gonna happen here you will connect the parents and if you connect
connect the parents and if you connect the power is what is going to happen is
力量将要发生的是，成为一个不是一棵树不，先生，你
the power is what is going to happen is that becoming a is not a tree no sir you
that becoming a is not a tree no sir you know that to be public because
知道要公开，因为我们会看到扭曲的影响非常
know that to be public because influences we will see in twist is very
influences we will see in twist is very easy all right
很简单，我们花在第二堂课上，所以如果您
easy all right we spend on lecture two so if you if the
we spend on lecture two so if you if the problem is a directed three PC you can
问题是定向三台PC，您可以将其转换为非定向树，并且
problem is a directed three PC you can transform it to a non directed tree and
transform it to a non directed tree and do everything extremely particularly
如果可以的话，请尽一切可能让您非常失望的树，因为您
do everything extremely particularly disappointed tree if you can because you
disappointed tree if you can because you wanna lies you get loops a lot is a
想要撒谎，你会经常循环，这是一个问题，有一种方法可以使
wanna lies you get loops a lot is a problem and there is a way to get a
problem and there is a way to get a harvest if you actually transform the
如果您实际上将诗歌转变为无向图，而是收获
harvest if you actually transform the poetry not to an undirected graph but
poetry not to an undirected graph but this dr. graph which is another type of
这个博士图，这是另一种类型的图，如果我们有几个图
this dr. graph which is another type of graph that you know if we have a few
graph that you know if we have a few minutes I'm going to show you how it
分钟，我将向您展示它看起来如何
minutes I'm going to show you how it looks like okay
looks like okay [Applause]
[掌声]
你想直接放鸽的原因不必说得好，让我选择
looks like okay [Applause]
the reason you want to make direct loft you don't have to say okay let me select
你想直接放鸽的原因不必说得好，让我选择
you don't have to say okay let me select this to be there with no and start
在那里没有，然后开始指向远离那里的箭头
this to be there with no and start pointing arrows away from there you know
pointing arrows away from there you know so we go this way and this this way and
所以我们以这种方式，以这种方式，然后以这种方式，但是你可以
so we go this way and this this way and then that way in that way but you can
then that way in that way but you can start reading note so you can produce
开始阅读笔记，以便您可以生成实际的有向图，但是它们是
start reading note so you can produce actually and directed graphs but they're
actually and directed graphs but they're not necessarily equivalent okay I do see
不一定相等，好吧，我确实没有任何理由会引起任何人的兴趣
not necessarily equivalent okay I do see no reason why anybody will be interested
no reason why anybody will be interested to transform an undirected graph to a
除非当然可以将无向图转换为有向图
to transform an undirected graph to a directed graph alright unless of course
directed graph alright unless of course you are trying to learn the causal
您正在尝试学习因果关系模型并在那里提供数据
you are trying to learn the causal relationship model and given data there
relationship model and given data there I can see a region in that case the
在那种情况下，我可以看到一个问题，这将成为高尔夫球选择
I can see a region in that case the problem will become a golf selection
problem will become a golf selection problem because you'll be asking which
问题，因为您将要问这些图中哪个更好地代表了
problem because you'll be asking which of these graphs better represents the
of these graphs better represents the data that I collected and that's an
我收集的数据，这是一个有趣的问题
data that I collected and that's an interesting problem all right
好吧，让我三分钟让我对问题做一个非常简单的事情
okay so let me three minutes let me do a very simple for the problem every
very simple for the problem every textbook in machine lambda graphical
机器lambda图形清漆中的教科书存在此问题，这是
textbook in machine lambda graphical varnish has this problem and this is a
varnish has this problem and this is a problem related to image the noising so
与图像噪声有关的问题，因此您可以认为流放呈现像素
problem related to image the noising so you can think exile presenting pixel
you can think exile presenting pixel values so that can be black or white
值，可以是黑色或白色，比如再见，亲爱的
values so that can be black or white let's say bye honey
let's say bye honey okay and of any mods and why I are what
好的，还有任何mod，为什么我是您所测量的，这些都是嘈杂的版本
okay and of any mods and why I are what you measured which are noisy versions of
you measured which are noisy versions of Exile right so you have an English but
放逐是正确的，所以您拥有英语，但只有一些嘈杂的版本
Exile right so you have an English but you only have some noisy version of it
you only have some noisy version of it that is represented by Y okay obviously
由Y表示的很明显，您知道您是否有图像
that is represented by Y okay obviously you know if you have an image
you know if you have an image if exercise we expect the neighbors to
如果进行运动，我们希望邻居是黑人，所以点击
if exercise we expect the neighbors to be black right so the clicks of the
be black right so the clicks of the Express sort of this sort of
这种相关性的表达方式就是您的点击次数
Express sort of this sort of correlations would be the click that you
correlations would be the click that you see here okay
看到这里好吧，显然XY和y是相关的
see here okay and obviously X Y and y I are correlated
and obviously X Y and y I are correlated because I envision what I to be a noisy
因为我预想我将成为X的嘈杂版本，所以如果您想添加
because I envision what I to be a noisy version of X are so if you want to add
version of X are so if you want to add the Joint Distribution of X I X &amp; Y or
XIX和Y的联合分布或形成X图片以及为什么图片
the Joint Distribution of X I X &amp; Y or form the X pictures and why pictures
form the X pictures and why pictures from this image basically you have a
从这个图像上，您基本上可以算出一个潜力产品
from this image basically you have a product of potentials that account for
product of potentials that account for the correlations of X i NX j alright and
X i NX j的相关性以及潜在的点击次数xi
the correlations of X i NX j alright and for potential define over the clicks x i
for potential define over the clicks x i and y which are this potential solution
和y这是这里的潜在解决方案
and y which are this potential solution here all right
再次是扮演剧透，而不是发挥这种潜力
again is to play the spoilers rather than or anything this potential
than or anything this potential exclusively is to find them because them
完全是为了找到它们，因为它们的能量消耗很大
exclusively is to find them because them down in terms of the energy of the
down in terms of the energy of the system and you remember that and
系统，您还记得，症状是减去负值的八分之一
system and you remember that and symptoms are eight to the minus the
symptoms are eight to the minus the energy so the energy here it will be
能量，所以这里的能量将由
energy so the energy here it will be defined by this little correlation on
defined by this little correlation on that I indicated before between X I and
我之前在XI和X a之间以及XI和YI之间指出的是这两个
that I indicated before between X I and X a and X I and Y I so those are the two
X a and X I and Y I so those are the two terms defined over the two cliques but
在两个集团中定义的术语，但它们不应该是天文学术语，即
terms defined over the two cliques but they shall not astronomy term that
they shall not astronomy term that involves summation for the extra light
涉及求和多余的光，通常在物理上是正确的
involves summation for the extra light okay and usually in physics right the
okay and usually in physics right the term is used to you know pixels in the
该术语用于了解模型中的像素，例如或浓度或
term is used to you know pixels in the model like or the concentration or
model like or the concentration or something like that is you sort of
这样的事情就是你可以描述原因的能力
something like that is you sort of characterizing reason all right you can
characterizing reason all right you can think of those X sorry one is not the
想起那些X对不起，这不是最大的集团权利，但你可以想到
think of those X sorry one is not the maximal clique right but you can think
maximal clique right but you can think it's known as a sub click so if you
这就是所谓的“子点击”，因此，如果您将一个额外的标签页往下扔，可以有人
it's known as a sub click so if you throw an extra tab down okay somebody
throw an extra tab down okay somebody can pose the problem using the data wire
可能会使用数据线来运行计算机参数而引起问题，但是正确的
can pose the problem using the data wire to run computers parameters but right
to run computers parameters but right now let's say you fix them and you don't
现在，假设您修复了它们，然后您不担心J的邻居和
now let's say you fix them and you don't you don't worry about J its neighbor and
you don't worry about J its neighbor and X I and why they relate together so I am
XI及其为何相互关联，所以我并不是说XI与之相关
X I and why they relate together so I am NOT saying that X I is related to that
NOT saying that X I is related to that but if you try to write the conditional
但是如果您尝试写条件分布，然后说我可以
but if you try to write the conditional distribution and you say if I can
distribution and you say if I can observe the whole image the noisy
观察整个图像的嘈杂版本为什么我可以计算X什么是X
observe the whole image the noisy version why can i compute X what X is
version why can i compute X what X is notice that all the x's are coupled with
请注意，所有x都与XS耦合，否则都在XS和XS中耦合。
notice that all the x's are coupled with the XS a couple with otherwise in both
the XS a couple with otherwise in both potential terms
潜在的条件好吧，所以当我们这样战斗时
potential terms all right so when we fight like this
all right so when we fight like this conditional you know this potential for
有条件的，你知道水明智的潜力，这使得
conditional you know this potential for water-wise right and this makes the
water-wise right and this makes the problem a little bit tricky on the way
这个问题在我们将要实施的方式上有点棘手，所以
problem a little bit tricky on the way we are going to implement oho me so to
we are going to implement oho me so to the trivial on bereavement to do this in
丧亲之琐碎的人可以在红灯下做到这一点，所以我们可以说
the trivial on bereavement to do this in red light so let's say that can we make
red light so let's say that can we make this a homework absolutely
这绝对是一件功课，只是让这更像是一个家
this a homework absolutely all right just make this a home more
all right just make this a home more because it's his red light I mean this I
因为这是他的红灯，我的意思是我必须激励Subic撰写
because it's his red light I mean this I have to motivate Subic to write the
have to motivate Subic to write the right homework or so you keep now it's
正确的作业，或者您现在就保留，那些即将成为热点的作业就来了
right homework or so you keep now it's coming of those become hot ones
coming of those become hot ones ok so here we are this is the original
好的，这是原始图像，用户通知非常干净，
ok so here we are this is the original image and user notice is very clean and
image and user notice is very clean and let's say you take the original image
假设您拍摄了原始图像，然后您从黑色干扰到了
let's say you take the original image and you perturb you know from black to
and you perturb you know from black to white white black 10% of the pixel
白色白色黑色像素服务图像的10％，这就是您所需要的
white white black 10% of the pixel services image and so that's what you
services image and so that's what you know so when you do this right you're
知道所以当您正确执行此操作时，您会问您是否要完成
know so when you do this right you're asking you know if you want to complete
asking you know if you want to complete with save this you say so you have X
与保存这个，你说，所以你给X给Y，你想找到那个
with save this you say so you have X given Y you want to find the x that
given Y you want to find the x that maximize is that posterior of X given Y
最大化是给定Y的X的后验，因此您做的事情要小得多，因此
maximize is that posterior of X given Y so what you do is much smaller so the
so what you do is much smaller so the probability is the same has been amazing
概率是相同的，这使系统的能量变得惊人，所以当您
probability is the same has been amazing the energy of the system so when you
the energy of the system so when you take a picture you can just back you
拍摄一张照片，您就可以轻松完成分享K的能量，现在让
take a picture you can just back you complete the energy you share K now let
complete the energy you share K now let me make it wide because the energy goes
我把它扩大，因为如果能量下降，现在能量就会消失，那么你保持它
me make it wide because the energy goes now if it goes down then you keep it
now if it goes down then you keep it wide and the reversal loops through the
宽，导演直接通过像素的反向循环将它们带到
wide and the reversal loops through the pixels right by the director bring them
pixels right by the director bring them up and down alright until you reach the
上下移动，直到达到最低能量，您就可以执行此操作
up and down alright until you reach the minimum energy you can do this
minimum energy you can do this no we
不，我们